{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:45:24.500685983+02:00","Elapsed":4411899655,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:45:24.514050419+02:00","Elapsed":2420214671,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:45:24.525671278+02:00","Elapsed":5434845466,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lC0BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"lC2BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:45:24.895073947+02:00","Elapsed":71202906,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bIoBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"bIqBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP8=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:05.916194459+02:00","Elapsed":209945764,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IdYBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"IdaBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:06.044600659+02:00","Elapsed":124393673,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qeMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"qeOBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:06.153517986+02:00","Elapsed":97805194,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"aZ0BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"aZ2BgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4/w==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:08.578732295+02:00","Elapsed":163699752,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ItkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"ItmBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:08.728605258+02:00","Elapsed":146001748,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wewBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"weyBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:46:08.828678296+02:00","Elapsed":89883750,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"H5cBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"H5eBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:48:59.138049526+02:00","Elapsed":5289843211,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"G3QBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"G3SBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.651201334+02:00","Elapsed":1987622901,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"G3QBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"G3SBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.660479199+02:00","Elapsed":2997572967,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zjwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"zjyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.669609901+02:00","Elapsed":2003580469,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zjwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"zjyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.669682773+02:00","Elapsed":3005232805,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zjwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"zjyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.675615828+02:00","Elapsed":281312,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QWQBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"QWSBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:32.698783574+02:00","Elapsed":5455201825,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:43.433849849+02:00","Elapsed":212756359,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:47.986238324+02:00","Elapsed":42511431,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YpwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"YpyBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Qdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:53.935385862+02:00","Elapsed":95977735,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YFIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAE=","Answer":"YFKBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAEDd3d3AmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAUAAQAADg8AEwZuZXd3ZWICY3MDdW5tA2VkdQAGbmV3d2ViAmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAEAAQAADg8ABEBqFBs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:54.165955404+02:00","Elapsed":333163847,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CpMBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"CpOBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADGcABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:56.724891863+02:00","Elapsed":55333834,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7BYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"7BaBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAL9QANB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABAAAL9QAE2BKoEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:56.995714672+02:00","Elapsed":89798778,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K64BAAABAAAAAAAABmh3LWNkbgx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"K66FgwABAAAAAQAABmh3LWNkbgx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEGaHctY2RuDHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXxlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyBmh3LWNkbgx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.500126139+02:00","Elapsed":255593,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NocBAAABAAAAAAAABXN0YXRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"NoeFgwABAAAAAQAABXN0YXRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEFc3RhdHMBZwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXxlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyBXN0YXRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||stats.g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.502273574+02:00","Elapsed":310645,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ZwBAAABAAAAAAAABW1lZGlhDHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4ZyFgwABAAAAAQAABW1lZGlhDHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAEAAQVtZWRpYQx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAAGAAEAAAAKAF4ZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgVtZWRpYQx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.526768961+02:00","Elapsed":312659,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xCUBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Fkcwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"xCWFgwABAAAAAQAAA2Fkcwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDYWRzDHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA2Fkcwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.526980228+02:00","Elapsed":253914,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oX0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"oX2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.527133806+02:00","Elapsed":403694,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"82IBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbg1kb3VibGVwaW1wc3NsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"82KFgwABAAAAAQAAA2Nkbg1kb3VibGVwaW1wc3NsA2NvbQAAAQABA2Nkbg1kb3VibGVwaW1wc3NsA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2RuDWRvdWJsZXBpbXBzc2wDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doublepimpssl.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.52723996+02:00","Elapsed":313792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IwQBAAABAAAAAAAABmh3LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"IwSBgAABAAIAAAAABmh3LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAAAQABBmh3LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAABQABAAAHiAAZCHZpcDB4MDRlA3NzbAZybmNkbjUDY29tAAh2aXAweDA0ZQNzc2wGcm5jZG41A2NvbQAAAQABAAAHiAAEzbnQTg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.646055469+02:00","Elapsed":144089013,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RZIBAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"RZKBgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAJUAGwxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAACVAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.671080639+02:00","Elapsed":144625259,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4sYBAAABAAAAAAAAE2NkbjFkLXN0YXRpYy1zaGFyZWQGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4saBgAABAAIAAAAAE2NkbjFkLXN0YXRpYy1zaGFyZWQGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAAAQABE2NkbjFkLXN0YXRpYy1zaGFyZWQGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAABQABAAAJ2QAZCHZpcDB4MDhlA3NzbAZybmNkbjUDY29tAAh2aXAweDA4ZQNzc2wGcm5jZG41A2NvbQAAAQABAAAJ2QAEzbnQjg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.804119113+02:00","Elapsed":276873220,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YsEBAAABAAAAAAAABGh1YnQHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"YsGBgAABAAEAAAAABGh1YnQHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQRodWJ0B3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAIiAATYEqgc","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.992463776+02:00","Elapsed":466026391,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/jIBAAABAAAAAAAAAmNpBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/jKBgAABAAIAAAAAAmNpBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQJjaQZwaG5jZG4DY29tAAAFAAEAAAHuABYFY3M4NTEDd3BjBnJuY2RuNANjb20ABWNzODUxA3dwYwZybmNkbjQDY29tAAABAAEAAAHuAASYwyJ2","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.99260363+02:00","Elapsed":465457706,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XPMBAAABAAAAAAAABnZ6LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"XPOBgAABAAIAAAAABnZ6LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAAAQABBnZ6LWNkbgpjb250ZW50YWJjA2NvbQAABQABAAAODwAWBWNzNzQxA3dwYwZybmNkbjQDY29tAAVjczc0MQN3cGMGcm5jZG40A2NvbQAAAQABAAAODwAEwOXd1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.99267319+02:00","Elapsed":490705029,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FpwBAAABAAAAAAAABGNkbjEIc21hbGxpbWcFcGhjZG4DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"FpyBgAABAAMAAAAABGNkbjEIc21hbGxpbWcFcGhjZG4DY29tAAABAAEEY2RuMQhzbWFsbGltZwVwaGNkbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsANhhIRFJlZGlyZWN0LUxCMy04OTA5Nzc2ODAJdXMtZWFzdC0xA2VsYglhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tABhIRFJlZGlyZWN0LUxCMy04OTA5Nzc2ODAJdXMtZWFzdC0xA2VsYglhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0VnrxGEhEUmVkaXJlY3QtTEIzLTg5MDk3NzY4MAl1cy1lYXN0LTEDZWxiCWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDQWWak=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.992722299+02:00","Elapsed":465815199,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"R64BAAABAAAAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"R66BgAABAAUAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNyYXcRZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABcGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2WAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwIU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:57.992783925+02:00","Elapsed":189441783,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5V4BAAABAAAAAAAAAmRpBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"5V6BgAABAAIAAAAAAmRpBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQJkaQZwaG5jZG4DY29tAAAFAAEAAAtSABkIdmlwMHgwOGUDc3NsBnJuY2RuNQNjb20ACHZpcDB4MDhlA3NzbAZybmNkbjUDY29tAAABAAEAAAtSAATNudCO","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.039339791+02:00","Elapsed":412615393,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9tcBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgZlbmdpbmUDcGhuCmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"9teFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NkbgZlbmdpbmUDcGhuCmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABAAEDY2RuBmVuZ2luZQNwaG4KZG91YmxlcGltcANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAZRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA2NkbgZlbmdpbmUDcGhuCmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.541485697+02:00","Elapsed":254862,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lLUBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"lLWBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEhABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEhAARCZgFfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEhAARKfUdfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEhAARKfYxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEhAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEhAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.679587419+02:00","Elapsed":138338349,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j6UBAAABAAAAAAAACHBsYXRmb3JtBnR1bWJscgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j6WBgAABAAIAAAAACHBsYXRmb3JtBnR1bWJscgNjb20AAAEAAQhwbGF0Zm9ybQZ0dW1ibHIDY29tAAAFAAEAAADuABcGY3MxMTQwA3dwYwZjaGljZG4DbmV0AAZjczExNDADd3BjBmNoaWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAO4ABJjHEys=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.751576659+02:00","Elapsed":210336306,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+5IBAAABAAAAAAAAAmNzBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"+5KBgAABAAIAAAAAAmNzBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQJjcwZwaG5jZG4DY29tAAAFAAEAAA4PABYFY3M4NTEDd3BjBnJuY2RuNANjb20ABWNzODUxA3dwYwZybmNkbjQDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAASYwyJ2","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.829572574+02:00","Elapsed":287841724,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QiQBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgVmZWVkcwd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"QiSBgAABAAQAAAAAA2NkbgVmZWVkcwd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAAAQABA2NkbgVmZWVkcwd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAABQABAAAA7wApA2NkbgVmZWVkcwd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQNjZG4JcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAADY2RuBWZlZWRzB3ZpZGVvc3oDY29tA2NkbglyZWZsZWN0ZWQDbmV0AAABAAEAAADvAARDFjBmA2NkbgVmZWVkcwd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQNjZG4JcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAAAAQABAAAA7wAEQxYwaANjZG4FZmVlZHMHdmlkZW9zegNjb20DY2RuCXJlZmxlY3RlZANuZXQAAAEAAQAAAO8ABEMWMGQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.8296706+02:00","Elapsed":221961772,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fvcBAAABAAAAAAAADWNkbjEtc21hbGxpbWcGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"fveBgAABAAIAAAAADWNkbjEtc21hbGxpbWcGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAAAQABDWNkbjEtc21hbGxpbWcGcGhuY2RuA2NvbQAABQABAAAODwAVCHNtYWxsaW1nBnBobmNkbgNjb20ACHNtYWxsaW1nBnBobmNkbgNjb20AAAEAAQAADg8ABNgSqBk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.82978349+02:00","Elapsed":221916759,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vsoBAAABAAAAAAAACHBsYXRmb3JtB3R3aXR0ZXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vsqBgAABAAYAAAAACHBsYXRmb3JtB3R3aXR0ZXIDY29tAAABAAEIcGxhdGZvcm0HdHdpdHRlcgNjb20AAAUAAQAAABUAGwVjczQ3MgN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AAVjczQ3MgN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAVACIMY3MxLWFwci04MzE1A3dhYwtlZGdlY2FzdGNkbgNuZXQADGNzMS1hcHItODMxNQN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAVAB4Dd2FjCGFwci04MzE1C2VkZ2VjYXN0ZG5zA25ldAADd2FjCGFwci04MzE1C2VkZ2VjYXN0ZG5zA25ldAAABQABAAAAFQAaCWNzMS1sYi1ldQQ4MzE1BWVjZG5zA25ldAAJY3MxLWxiLWV1BDgzMTUFZWNkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAVABoEY3M0MQN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AARjczQxA3dhYwtlZGdlY2FzdGNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAABUABF243EI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.829905981+02:00","Elapsed":239169937,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eygBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"eyiBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAABKwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPiw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.898057553+02:00","Elapsed":146687801,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SKoBAAABAAAAAAAAAm0yBW5zaW1nA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"SKqBgAABAAQAAAAAAm0yBW5zaW1nA25ldAAAAQABAm0yBW5zaW1nA25ldAAAAQABAAAAtwAEz7IASAJtMgVuc2ltZwNuZXQAAAEAAQAAALcABM+yAEsCbTIFbnNpbWcDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC3AATPsgBFAm0yBW5zaW1nA25ldAAAAQABAAAAtwAEz7IARg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:58.998323309+02:00","Elapsed":246975707,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"91cBAAABAAAAAAAABGFkczIKY29udGVudGFiYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"91eFgwABAAAAAQAABGFkczIKY29udGVudGFiYwNjb20AAAEAAQRhZHMyCmNvbnRlbnRhYmMDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgRhZHMyCmNvbnRlbnRhYmMDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||ads2.contentabc.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.083313264+02:00","Elapsed":240626,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SeoBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgVuaWNoZQd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"SeqBgAABAAQAAAAAA2NkbgVuaWNoZQd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAAAQABA2NkbgVuaWNoZQd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQAABQABAAAAyQApA2NkbgVuaWNoZQd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQNjZG4JcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAADY2RuBW5pY2hlB3ZpZGVvc3oDY29tA2NkbglyZWZsZWN0ZWQDbmV0AAABAAEAAADJAARDFjBkA2NkbgVuaWNoZQd2aWRlb3N6A2NvbQNjZG4JcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAAAAQABAAAAyQAEQxYwZgNjZG4FbmljaGUHdmlkZW9zegNjb20DY2RuCXJlZmxlY3RlZANuZXQAAAEAAQAAAMkABEMWMGg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.083470213+02:00","Elapsed":242453970,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DGsBAAABAAAAAAAAB3R3aXR0ZXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DGuBgAABAAIAAAAAB3R3aXR0ZXIDY29tAAABAAEHdHdpdHRlcgNjb20AAAEAAQAABkUABGj0KoEHdHdpdHRlcgNjb20AAAEAAQAABkUABGj0KgE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.203473442+02:00","Elapsed":120382008,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bSQBAAABAAAAAAAABGNkbjEDYWRzCmNvbnRlbnRhYmMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bSSBgAABAAIAAAAABGNkbjEDYWRzCmNvbnRlbnRhYmMDY29tAAABAAEEY2RuMQNhZHMKY29udGVudGFiYwNjb20AAAUAAQAADZYAGQh2aXAweDA0ZQNzc2wGcm5jZG41A2NvbQAIdmlwMHgwNGUDc3NsBnJuY2RuNQNjb20AAAEAAQAADZYABM250E4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.212046468+02:00","Elapsed":128823971,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vakBAAABAAAAAAAAB2h3LWNkbjIKY29udGVudGFiYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"vamBgAABAAIAAAAAB2h3LWNkbjIKY29udGVudGFiYwNjb20AAAEAAQdody1jZG4yCmNvbnRlbnRhYmMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAmzABkIdmlwMHgwNGUDc3NsBnJuY2RuNQNjb20ACHZpcDB4MDRlA3NzbAZybmNkbjUDY29tAAABAAEAAAmzAATNudBO","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.220429987+02:00","Elapsed":137358617,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kcgBAAABAAAAAAAAAXAHdHdpdHRlcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"kciBgwABAAAAAQAAAXAHdHdpdHRlcgNjb20AAAEAAQd0d2l0dGVyA2NvbQAABgABAAAAOwA/A25zMQNwMjYGZHluZWN0A25ldAAKem9uZS1hZG1pbgZkeW5kbnMDY29tAHeijRUAAA4QAAACWAAJOoAAAAA8","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.233063757+02:00","Elapsed":149798272,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s7YBAAABAAAAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAE=","Answer":"s7aBgAABAAEAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAEFbGlwc2kCY2EAAAEAAQAADhAABKCZTSU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:58:59.270424537+02:00","Elapsed":88283813,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+zoBAAABAAAAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"+zqBgAABAAIAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQVkZW1vcwl3aXJlZGRvdHMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA7AA8Jd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAJd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEIs4M1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:03.437855684+02:00","Elapsed":66191938,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Wh0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Wh2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQN3d3cDem5jAml0AAABAAEAAA4QAATBvXAq","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:03.492080782+02:00","Elapsed":56548104,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uQsBAAABAAAAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"uQuBgAABAAIAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABCGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABAAABKwAEaBh6UQhjc2VydmljZQh1bmRlcm5ldANvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYe1E=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:04.623763311+02:00","Elapsed":87304054,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fUUBAAABAAAAAAAADHZhY2FuZWVkYXNhcANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"fUWBgAABAAIAAAAADHZhY2FuZWVkYXNhcANjb20AAAEAAQx2YWNhbmVlZGFzYXADY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARoGeIGDHZhY2FuZWVkYXNhcANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgZ4wY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:05.37720794+02:00","Elapsed":75537504,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YIUBAAABAAAAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"YIWBgAABAAEAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQl3aXJlZGRvdHMObWV0YWxvZ2ljc3NvZnQDY29tAAABAAEAAASvAAREQXpn","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:12.652311704+02:00","Elapsed":68890587,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NDkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgVteHBubANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"NDmFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NkbgVteHBubANjb20AAAEAAQNjZG4FbXhwbmwDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFUZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgNjZG4FbXhwbmwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mxpnl.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:17.810349497+02:00","Elapsed":221911,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MfsBAAABAAAAAAAAAWEFdmZndGIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"MfuBgAABAAMAAAAAAWEFdmZndGIDY29tAAABAAEBYQV2Zmd0YgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAFA5tb2RlbnRzLWRpYW5jZQNjb20ADm1vZGVudHMtZGlhbmNlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEI58FdA5tb2RlbnRzLWRpYW5jZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOdw9Y=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:17.86704419+02:00","Elapsed":123737387,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"61QBAAABAAAAAAAAAXQFZnJ0eWsDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"61SBgAABAAEAAAAAAXQFZnJ0eWsDY29tAAABAAEBdAVmcnR5awNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABGuy8m0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:18.497240244+02:00","Elapsed":72198777,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LIMBAAABAAAAAAAACGNrc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"LIOBgAABAAMAAAAACGNrc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABCGNrc3RhdGljA2NvbQAABQABAAAA+QAYA2NkcwhoM2EyejV6NQVod2NkbgNuZXQAA2NkcwhoM2EyejV6NQVod2NkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAPkABM252AoDY2RzCGgzYTJ6NXo1BWh3Y2RuA25ldAAAAQABAAAA+QAEzbnYKg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:19.030326066+02:00","Elapsed":184555661,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"sckBAAABAAAAAAAABW1kZXp3CWxvY2Fsc2x1dARjbHViAAABAAE=","Answer":"scmBgAABAAIAAAAABW1kZXp3CWxvY2Fsc2x1dARjbHViAAABAAEFbWRlencJbG9jYWxzbHV0BGNsdWIAAAUAAQAAASsAEQJqMQhqdW1wNGdlbwNjb20AAmoxCGp1bXA0Z2VvA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAENNNfxg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:20.888342239+02:00","Elapsed":92700966,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QegBAAABAAAAAAAAD2RhdGluZ3NlYXJjaHBybwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QeiBgAABAAIAAAAAD2RhdGluZ3NlYXJjaHBybwNjb20AAAEAAQ9kYXRpbmdzZWFyY2hwcm8DY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0HF8XD2RhdGluZ3NlYXJjaHBybwNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDQdN0E=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:21.21139294+02:00","Elapsed":86680135,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9KwBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"9KyBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADdcABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADdcABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADdcABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADdcABLncuAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:30.242765065+02:00","Elapsed":326411,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"b/0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"b/2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAAPIABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAAPIABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:30.456699654+02:00","Elapsed":287076,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"suEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"suGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAAgAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAAAIABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAACAAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAAgAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:30.461957764+02:00","Elapsed":321440,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/esBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"/euFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:30.463859626+02:00","Elapsed":201975,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5qkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"5qmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIanVnZ2Nhc2gDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAATYEqhP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:30.556452404+02:00","Elapsed":92842516,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eP4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"eP6FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:31.476582289+02:00","Elapsed":325048,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ceEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ceGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:31.476982881+02:00","Elapsed":238063,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CT8BAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"CT+BgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:31.577848235+02:00","Elapsed":105713311,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qB0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"qB2BgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zmMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zmoDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zmgDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zmcDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zmkDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGQABEp9zpM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:31.729894663+02:00","Elapsed":253604265,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t0cBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t0eBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADDcABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:45.121376024+02:00","Elapsed":360179,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6+MBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"6+OBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABwcAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:45.289706808+02:00","Elapsed":157775472,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"INwBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"INyBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADg8AIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADg8AIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:45.348051849+02:00","Elapsed":54685532,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v44BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"v46BgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADDEABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:50.822107559+02:00","Elapsed":244172,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pcUBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"pcWBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABwIAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:50.848208564+02:00","Elapsed":250099,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+uwBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"+uyBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADgoAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADgoAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:50.885765387+02:00","Elapsed":580887,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:52.039382337+02:00","Elapsed":41191081,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"voQBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"voSBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADCwABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:55.8989444+02:00","Elapsed":218854,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C/wBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"C/yBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABv0AOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:55.904608389+02:00","Elapsed":302561,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RjcBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"RjeBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADgUAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADgUAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T19:59:55.910555672+02:00","Elapsed":183312,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0qEBAAABAAAAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"0qGBgAABAAQAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAENY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAABMAJA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATACUNY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABsEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEFzkYEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:27.824794464+02:00","Elapsed":326304301,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rtwBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"rtyBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADAsABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:29.103305832+02:00","Elapsed":180445,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/AQBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"/ASBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABtwAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:29.188642415+02:00","Elapsed":222780,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JRwBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"JRyBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADeQAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADeQAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:29.200944296+02:00","Elapsed":237576,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"aEIBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"aEKBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADAkABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:30.94974402+02:00","Elapsed":243380,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P44BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"P46BgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABtoAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:30.959190783+02:00","Elapsed":259958,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jikBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"jimBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADeIAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADeIAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:00:30.977625215+02:00","Elapsed":374773,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:02:32.657624529+02:00","Elapsed":149301691,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QekBAAABAAAAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"QemBgAABAAQAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4AwNhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQDYXBpCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgBA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4Ag==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:04:33.177841256+02:00","Elapsed":251130300,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOUBAAABAAAAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOWBgAABAAEAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABDHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAARwAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:05:21.281324432+02:00","Elapsed":27226757905,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOUBAAABAAAAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOWBgAABAAEAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABDHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAzQAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:05:21.295016293+02:00","Elapsed":30248283118,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOUBAAABAAAAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOWBgAABAAEAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABDHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAcQAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:05:21.295105784+02:00","Elapsed":15233802681,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOUBAAABAAAAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOWBgAABAAEAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABDHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAArQAEQOm4Xw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:05:21.295202687+02:00","Elapsed":29247733422,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOUBAAABAAAAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOWBgAABAAEAAAAADHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABDHNhZmVicm93c2luZwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAFwAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:05:21.295286896+02:00","Elapsed":23218626183,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ftcBAAABAAAAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"fteBgAABAAQAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEEbWVzdQVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAA4AHwhtZXN1LWNkbgVhcHBsZQNjb20GYWthZG5zA25ldAAIbWVzdS1jZG4FYXBwbGUDY29tBmFrYWRucwNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAA4AFARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20ABG1lc3UBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEEf03zgRtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAA4ABBH9NdI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:07:01.799909649+02:00","Elapsed":29080985559,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ftcBAAABAAAAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"fteBgAABAAQAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEEbWVzdQVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAA4AHwhtZXN1LWNkbgVhcHBsZQNjb20GYWthZG5zA25ldAAIbWVzdS1jZG4FYXBwbGUDY29tBmFrYWRucwNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAA4AFARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20ABG1lc3UBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEEf03zARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAA4ABBH9N88=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:07:01.813981667+02:00","Elapsed":26086480771,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ftcBAAABAAAAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"fteBgAABAAQAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEEbWVzdQVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAA4AHwhtZXN1LWNkbgVhcHBsZQNjb20GYWthZG5zA25ldAAIbWVzdS1jZG4FYXBwbGUDY29tBmFrYWRucwNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAA4AFARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20ABG1lc3UBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEEf01ygRtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAA4ABBH9N88=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:07:01.815898443+02:00","Elapsed":28092324958,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ftcBAAABAAAAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"fteBgAABAAQAAAAABG1lc3UFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEEbWVzdQVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAA4AHwhtZXN1LWNkbgVhcHBsZQNjb20GYWthZG5zA25ldAAIbWVzdS1jZG4FYXBwbGUDY29tBmFrYWRucwNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAA4AFARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20ABG1lc3UBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEEf010ARtZXN1AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAA4ABBH9Ncw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:07:01.823382922+02:00","Elapsed":22093267961,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Xm8BAAABAAAAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Xm+BgAABAAYAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEKdGltZS1tYWNvcwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAHcAGAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/Tb9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9In0IdGltZS1vc3gBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdwAEEf00fQh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/TT9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9Nn0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:07:51.220562704+02:00","Elapsed":198545850,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DxIBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DxKBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAACkAABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:08.350036449+02:00","Elapsed":306391,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JUQBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"JUSBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABRAAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:08.359952072+02:00","Elapsed":238299,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3wEBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"3wGBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADBgAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADBgAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:08.367041864+02:00","Elapsed":304857,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EQ8BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EQ+BgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAACjcABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:17.380550936+02:00","Elapsed":138694,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lt8BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"lt+BgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABQcAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:17.383641084+02:00","Elapsed":124525,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pI8BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"pI+BgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADA8AIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADA8AIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:17.391025205+02:00","Elapsed":123656,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"23IBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"23KBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAACjYABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:18.306802709+02:00","Elapsed":246237,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"a80BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"a82BgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABQYAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:18.343470042+02:00","Elapsed":239116,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"y+EBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"y+GBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADA4AIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADA4AIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:18.380424045+02:00","Elapsed":257338,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"d3sBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"d3uBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAJwgANB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABAAAJwgAE2BKoEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:20.670780127+02:00","Elapsed":265316,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1lgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"1liBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABQQAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:20.776574045+02:00","Elapsed":242133,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x6QBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"x6SBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADAwAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADAwAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:20.781543721+02:00","Elapsed":253484,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JRYBAAABAAAAAAAABXZhbGlkBWFwcGxlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JRaBgAABAAQAAAAABXZhbGlkBWFwcGxlA2NvbQAAAQABBXZhbGlkBWFwcGxlA2NvbQAABQABAAAADgAjBXZhbGlkDG9yaWdpbi1hcHBsZQNjb20GYWthZG5zA25ldAAFdmFsaWQMb3JpZ2luLWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAOABsLdmFsaWQtYXBwbGUBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQALdmFsaWQtYXBwbGUBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEEf01zQt2YWxpZC1hcHBsZQFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAAOAAQR/TXR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:08:46.254589474+02:00","Elapsed":333957296,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/CsBAAABAAAAAAAAB25lY29sYXMGZ2l0aHViAmlvAAABAAE=","Answer":"/CuBgAABAAQAAAAAB25lY29sYXMGZ2l0aHViAmlvAAABAAEHbmVjb2xhcwZnaXRodWICaW8AAAEAAQAADg8ABLnHbpkHbmVjb2xhcwZnaXRodWICaW8AAAEAAQAADg8ABLnHb5kHbmVjb2xhcwZnaXRodWICaW8AAAEAAQAADg8ABLnHbJkHbmVjb2xhcwZnaXRodWICaW8AAAEAAQAADg8ABLnHbZk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:14.044532688+02:00","Elapsed":176700727,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WWkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WWmBgAABAAMAAAAAA2NkbgtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQNjZG4LbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATACEDY2RuC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADY2RuC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAYBWUyMjAxAWcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUyMjAxAWcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAABMABBfTCGw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:14.408085027+02:00","Elapsed":121396410,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:14.920307667+02:00","Elapsed":47489809,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x/wBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"x/yBgAABAAMAAAAABnNlY3VyZQtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQZzZWN1cmULbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATACQGc2VjdXJlC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAGc2VjdXJlC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAaBWUyMjAxA2tzZApha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAFZTIyMDEDa3NkCmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAASs41jE","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:15.093555509+02:00","Elapsed":133370830,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Tu8BAAABAAAAAAAACGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Tu+BgAABAAMAAAAACGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAAAQABCGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmCGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAIYWNjb3VudHMLbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABgFZTIyMDEBYgpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAFZTIyMDEBYgpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEF9MIbA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:15.591180473+02:00","Elapsed":67411672,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"R40BAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"R42BgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAREAGwxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAERAARCZgFf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:16.666559698+02:00","Elapsed":49889620,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hj0BAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"hj2BgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAUAAQAAALkAGwxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAC5AAStwkxe","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:17.259324756+02:00","Elapsed":130459737,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VS8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3BheQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"VS+BgAABAAQAAAAAA3BheQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA3BheQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4BANwYXkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEDcGF5CHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgCA3BheQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4Aw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:25.96799016+02:00","Elapsed":140140180,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j1sBAAABAAAAAAAABGF1dGgId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j1uBgAABAAQAAAAABGF1dGgId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQRhdXRoCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgBBGF1dGgId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIEYXV0aAh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4AwRhdXRoCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgE","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:09:26.141581731+02:00","Elapsed":130977736,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jm8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"jm+BgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAJMQANB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABAAAJMQAE2BKoEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:45.911891715+02:00","Elapsed":322077,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eDUBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"eDWBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABHMAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:45.915095399+02:00","Elapsed":176296,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZrIBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"ZrKBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAAC3sAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAAC3sAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:45.92182349+02:00","Elapsed":242368,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iewBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ieyBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:52.911264786+02:00","Elapsed":272646326,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+I0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"+I2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAFABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAABQAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAFABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:52.925170375+02:00","Elapsed":286301595,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AV8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"AV+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:52.956224583+02:00","Elapsed":320173006,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tksBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"tkuBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA5wAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5wAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5wAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:52.968615902+02:00","Elapsed":329947963,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Hw0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Hw2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:53.62032612+02:00","Elapsed":199655,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"is8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"is+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:53.622527699+02:00","Elapsed":226146,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bfgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"bfiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:53.622648156+02:00","Elapsed":270083,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gJ4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gJ6BgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTGMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTGgDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTGcDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTGkDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTGoDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABK3CTJM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:53.664991681+02:00","Elapsed":39968448,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"y0MBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"y0OBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:10:53.67288814+02:00","Elapsed":55039711,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PFUBAAABAAAAAAAABmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PFWBgAABAAIAAAAABmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAHv1wBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:56.083441955+02:00","Elapsed":195347322,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KXcBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KXeBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.073531145+02:00","Elapsed":125566690,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8ZgBAAABAAAAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"8ZiBgAABAAUAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQABCmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.213908522+02:00","Elapsed":266011075,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZHcBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ZHeBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.215622909+02:00","Elapsed":267667343,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Dh8BAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Dh+BgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.265497234+02:00","Elapsed":240844869,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wJwBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wJyBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.298682613+02:00","Elapsed":350723745,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VkkBAAABAAAAAAAACWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"VkmFgwABAAAAAQAACWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABAAEJY29sbGVjdG9yCWdpdGh1YmFwcANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAXxlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyCWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||collector.githubapp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:57.991760998+02:00","Elapsed":289953,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WQ0BAAABAAAAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"WQ2BgAABAAUAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:58.074254032+02:00","Elapsed":114589177,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TnkBAAABAAAAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"TnmBgAABAAIAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAEMZ2l0aHViLWNsb3VkAnMzCWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFgZzMy0xLXcJYW1hem9uYXdzA2NvbQAGczMtMS13CWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAAUABDTYqZs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:58.102022557+02:00","Elapsed":141638955,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qZ8BAAABAAAAAAAAA2FwaQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"qZ+BgAABAAIAAAAAA2FwaQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAEDYXBpBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XQDYXBpBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:11:58.609696441+02:00","Elapsed":112795979,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NaYBAAABAAAAAAAABGNhbW8RZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NaaBgAABAAUAAAAABGNhbW8RZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAABAAEEY2FtbxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAUAAQAAAB0AFwZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2UAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlQIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZYCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2XAhQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:08.851443565+02:00","Elapsed":213037801,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MJ4BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"MJ6BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAB0ABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:21.876626937+02:00","Elapsed":257487713,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+6UBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"+6WBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:21.946260364+02:00","Elapsed":319305129,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+6UBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"+6WBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:22.026642095+02:00","Elapsed":146254707,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wKwBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"wKyBgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMfUAC4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMcFGi4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMdHAC4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:22.348442576+02:00","Elapsed":132171474,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"00MBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"00OBgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAqQAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAMQAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAEwAAAAAAAAAAAEY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:22.455528686+02:00","Elapsed":205649032,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y68BAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Y6+BgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:42.407370242+02:00","Elapsed":250932685,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hXUBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"hXWBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:42.413024325+02:00","Elapsed":256556243,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"49gBAAABAAAAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"49iBgAABAAUAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQABCmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:42.413203413+02:00","Elapsed":260315953,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yNYBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"yNaBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:42.413302872+02:00","Elapsed":257701552,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3c4BAAABAAAAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"3c6BgAABAAUAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:43.210449367+02:00","Elapsed":51294723,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1EYBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"1EaBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:43.210735884+02:00","Elapsed":49467264,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7K0BAAABAAAAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"7K2BgAABAAIAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAEMZ2l0aHViLWNsb3VkAnMzCWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFgZzMy0xLXcJYW1hem9uYXdzA2NvbQAGczMtMS13CWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAAUABDTYaFs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:12:43.220453369+02:00","Elapsed":53001933,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qroBAAABAAAAAAAAAzE3MwI0MAMyMjACMzQHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAE=","Answer":"qrqBgAABAAEAAAAAAzE3MwI0MAMyMjACMzQHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAEDMTczAjQwAzIyMAIzNAdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQAAASsAMxFlYzItMzQtMjIwLTQwLTE3Mwl1cy13ZXN0LTIHY29tcHV0ZQlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:15.189338617+02:00","Elapsed":190430820,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xogBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"xoiBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:21.640278468+02:00","Elapsed":49004654,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Xy8BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"Xy+BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAwAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAwABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:52.267661048+02:00","Elapsed":178724249,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rUEBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"rUGBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAA4AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:52.314573991+02:00","Elapsed":41547167,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rUEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"rUGBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:52.360330214+02:00","Elapsed":269318481,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PwUBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBmxhY25pYwNuZXQAABwAAQ==","Answer":"PwWBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBmxhY25pYwNuZXQAABwAAQV3aG9pcwZsYWNuaWMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAA4QAAwGbGFjbmljA25ldAAGbGFjbmljA25ldAAAHAABAAAOEAAQIAETx3ACQAAAAAAAAAAAEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:53.130429776+02:00","Elapsed":512568613,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j10BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBmxhY25pYwNuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j12BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBmxhY25pYwNuZXQAAAEAAQV3aG9pcwZsYWNuaWMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAA4QAAwGbGFjbmljA25ldAAGbGFjbmljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOEAAEyAMOCg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:53.262637071+02:00","Elapsed":646290830,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j10BAAABAAAAAAAABmxhY25pYwNuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j12BgAABAAEAAAAABmxhY25pYwNuZXQAAAEAAQZsYWNuaWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4QAATIAw4K","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:53.433908509+02:00","Elapsed":268179113,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F54BAAABAAAAAAAAAjE2AzE2MQMyMDIDMTg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"F56BgwABAAAAAQAAAjE2AzE2MQMyMDIDMTg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAzE2MQMyMDIDMTg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAABgABAAAGHwBDA25zMQdsb2Nhd2ViA2NvbQJicgAKcG9zdG1hc3Rlcgdsb2Nhd2ViA2NvbQJicgB3ztJ5AAAOEAAAAlgAEnUAAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:13:55.453527486+02:00","Elapsed":275268205,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/MMBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/MOBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAA4QAATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:14:24.627640173+02:00","Elapsed":264743342,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8rQBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQ==","Answer":"8rSBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAHBwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:14:24.741189124+02:00","Elapsed":109769679,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9/oBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"9/qBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAHBwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:14:24.94784558+02:00","Elapsed":158311547,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XVcBAAABAAAAAAAAAzIyOQMyNDcDMTA5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQ==","Answer":"XVeBgAABAAEAAAAAAzIyOQMyNDcDMTA5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQMyMjkDMjQ3AzEwOQMxOTMHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAEAAA4QAA4DZGV2BHVjb3oDbmV0AA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:14:29.299963048+02:00","Elapsed":165110021,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"M8QBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"M8SBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAAxAAATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:04.711663641+02:00","Elapsed":5260750943,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gB0BAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQ==","Answer":"gB2BgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAHBwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:04.804975332+02:00","Elapsed":89064934,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9h8BAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"9h+BgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAGKwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:04.88580737+02:00","Elapsed":71908703,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"M8QBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"M8SBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAAw8AATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:09.501046372+02:00","Elapsed":5043949845,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7GkBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"7GmBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAAwWAATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:47.438908714+02:00","Elapsed":233974,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CpkBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQ==","Answer":"CpmBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAG3QA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:47.446595286+02:00","Elapsed":182912,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NscBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"NseBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAGAQA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:18:47.450587239+02:00","Elapsed":216309,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gyEBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gyGBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAA4QAATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:17.712341334+02:00","Elapsed":5278223935,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gyEBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gyGBgAABAAEAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAAEAAQp3bWNvbnZpcnVzBW5hcm9kAnJ1AAABAAEAAA4QAATBbffl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:17.76841699+02:00","Elapsed":366399203,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2AIBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQ==","Answer":"2AKBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAABwAAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAHBwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:17.860180961+02:00","Elapsed":141489831,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vrkBAAABAAAAAAAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"vrmBgAABAAAAAQAACndtY29udmlydXMFbmFyb2QCcnUAAA8AAQVuYXJvZAJydQAABgABAAAHBwA0A25zMQR1Y296A25ldAAIZG5zYWRtaW4EdWNvegJydQB4SXiUAAAqMAAABwgAJ40AAAAqMA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:17.996391544+02:00","Elapsed":90150060,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YxoBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"YxqBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADg8ABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:32.134877832+02:00","Elapsed":199759241,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3PABAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"3PCBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABwcAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:32.187967298+02:00","Elapsed":49398506,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBABAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"HBCBgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADg8AIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADg8AIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:21:32.245119692+02:00","Elapsed":50867569,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"44wBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"44yBgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADfIABNgSqBA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:22:01.763832317+02:00","Elapsed":268082,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+TgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"+TiBgAABAAAAAQAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAYAAQAABuoAOgVzZG5zMwh1bHRyYWRucwNuZXQAA2RucwhtaW5kZ2VlawNjb20AeAu6UAAAcIAAABwgABJ1AAAAqMA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:22:01.767150863+02:00","Elapsed":151525,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"d10BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"d12BgAABAAIAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADfIAIgAKDG14Yi0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQAHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAA8AAQAADfIAIgAKDG14YS0wMDJhMDcwMQRnc2xiCHBwaG9zdGVkA2NvbQA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:22:01.773990643+02:00","Elapsed":206902,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yToBAAABAAAAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"yTqBgAABAAQAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAENY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAABMAJA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATACUNY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABsEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEX2Q8Rw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:22:12.317157008+02:00","Elapsed":251662123,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:26:03.516852718+02:00","Elapsed":6303153272,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NaIBAAABAAAAAAAAAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"NaKBgAABAAEAAAAAAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAAAOEAAdB2hvc3QtNDECMzgBNwMyMzQGdGVkYXRhA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:09.126678838+02:00","Elapsed":5276784506,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NaIBAAABAAAAAAAAAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"NaKBgAABAAEAAAAAAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAzIzNAE3AjM4AjQxB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAAAOEAAdB2hvc3QtNDECMzgBNwMyMzQGdGVkYXRhA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:09.184317604+02:00","Elapsed":340652418,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mpQBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEzMQIyNQMyNDQDMTg1B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"mpSBgwABAAAAAQAAAzEzMQIyNQMyNDQDMTg1B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAABAjI1AzI0NAMxODUHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAGAAEAAAQyAEwDbnMxC2t2c29sdXRpb25zAm5sAApob3N0bWFzdGVyAjI1AzI0NAMxODUHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAHhJzOcAADhAAAAOEAASdQAAAVGA","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:13.22360991+02:00","Elapsed":86223389,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XX4BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"XX6BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAAUAECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:14.205248217+02:00","Elapsed":62283507,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fwUBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"fwWBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAABEAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAABEABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:14.207093066+02:00","Elapsed":65718647,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/xwBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"/xyBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAABAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAADhAABMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:14.649219987+02:00","Elapsed":122626389,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"V14BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"V16BgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:28:14.655232742+02:00","Elapsed":128665329,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0VABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"0VCFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:30:41.344200129+02:00","Elapsed":590371,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2q8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2q+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:30:41.468202867+02:00","Elapsed":317868,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kAkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"kAmFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:30:41.482810982+02:00","Elapsed":273892,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qt4BAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"qt6BgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.175832673+02:00","Elapsed":21830764142,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uLwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uLyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD5MDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD2MDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD2oDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD2cDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD2gDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAMQABGyxD2k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.176082265+02:00","Elapsed":19792571635,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qt4BAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"qt6BgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.17613195+02:00","Elapsed":22832528029,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K2YBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K2aBgAABAAcAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMgAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.190443731+02:00","Elapsed":22853173285,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K2YBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K2aBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABIwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.216769921+02:00","Elapsed":23881063255,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K2YBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K2aBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAXwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAXwAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.218696499+02:00","Elapsed":20862214713,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K2YBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K2aBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA0gAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0gAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0gAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0gAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0gAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.218757683+02:00","Elapsed":16860782229,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uLwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uLyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zmgDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zmkDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zmMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zmoDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zmcDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAABIABEp9zpM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.22078029+02:00","Elapsed":22877116973,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uLwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uLyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD2oDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD5MDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD2kDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD2cDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD2MDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAGIABGyxD2g=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.220828209+02:00","Elapsed":21874790101,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bNsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bNuBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.227882416+02:00","Elapsed":22890676427,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bNsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bNuBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.22793392+02:00","Elapsed":16870252254,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bNsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bNuBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.22797129+02:00","Elapsed":23898576454,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v0EBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"v0GBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.228017547+02:00","Elapsed":23899378228,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bNsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bNuBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.22804667+02:00","Elapsed":20871606141,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v0EBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"v0GBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.24575875+02:00","Elapsed":20890544898,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qt4BAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"qt6BgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.245904319+02:00","Elapsed":19893435613,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jq0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jq2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.245916076+02:00","Elapsed":20889484777,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v0EBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"v0GBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.245979322+02:00","Elapsed":22913129939,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v0EBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"v0GBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.246033407+02:00","Elapsed":16889721526,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jq0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jq2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.246106288+02:00","Elapsed":16888389936,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jq0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jq2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.24615508+02:00","Elapsed":23910449276,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jq0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jq2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.250485577+02:00","Elapsed":22913227870,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uLwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uLyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTGgDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTGMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTGkDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTJMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTGcDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAFcABK3CTGo=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:31:04.404378895+02:00","Elapsed":16044242732,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uLwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uLyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTJMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTGcDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTGoDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTGMDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTGgDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANgABK3CTGk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.518674664+02:00","Elapsed":96158507057,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K2YBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K2aBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA3AAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA3AAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA3AAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA3AAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.522010591+02:00","Elapsed":97184046966,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bNsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"bNuBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAANMABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAANMABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.526675182+02:00","Elapsed":97188905194,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v0EBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"v0GBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.540542639+02:00","Elapsed":97203082795,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Yc0BAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"Yc2BgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAB8kABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.54437673+02:00","Elapsed":5864628229,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jq0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jq2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.552799798+02:00","Elapsed":97215034691,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ph4BAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ph6BgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.552911275+02:00","Elapsed":5874748531,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PTQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PTSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.557488114+02:00","Elapsed":5874295957,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Yc0BAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"Yc2BgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAB8kABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.882336369+02:00","Elapsed":5183997769,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ph4BAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ph6BgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.882445996+02:00","Elapsed":5184457259,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ph4BAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ph6BgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.882560315+02:00","Elapsed":3201817035,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PTQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PTSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.885596727+02:00","Elapsed":5187249782,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Yc0BAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"Yc2BgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAB8kABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.885702165+02:00","Elapsed":3202594623,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PTQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PTSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.888169259+02:00","Elapsed":3204689209,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EEIBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"EEKBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0wAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAANMABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.92925523+02:00","Elapsed":1671838064,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hAYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"hAaBgAABAAcAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAewAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAESn1HXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAewAEQOmnXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.932452834+02:00","Elapsed":1675037922,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"h0QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"h0SBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:32.94461155+02:00","Elapsed":1685101493,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hAYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"hAaBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAQAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.073996667+02:00","Elapsed":806099557,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EEIBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"EEKBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.085671133+02:00","Elapsed":2827429790,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"h0QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"h0SBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.087550287+02:00","Elapsed":814540498,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MisBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"MiuBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.087696629+02:00","Elapsed":1825000108,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MisBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"MiuBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.108619711+02:00","Elapsed":835579517,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EEIBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"EEKBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA0gAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAANIABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:32:33.470581075+02:00","Elapsed":204129958,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"absBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"abuBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4/w==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:12.989883032+02:00","Elapsed":324659231,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zy8BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"zy+FgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:12.990082081+02:00","Elapsed":337388318,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OKYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"OKaBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:13.115039083+02:00","Elapsed":84504727,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NLMBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"NLOFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:13.115197468+02:00","Elapsed":84873647,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"dYeBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:13.204252107+02:00","Elapsed":85692160,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4y4BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"4y6FgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:33:13.20441399+02:00","Elapsed":85950671,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UH0BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"UH2BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAAUAECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.081741838+02:00","Elapsed":2361940788,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DLEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"DLGBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAkAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAkABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.08203491+02:00","Elapsed":5363627361,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DLEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"DLGBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAUABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.089827346+02:00","Elapsed":4368934753,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DLEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"DLGBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAUABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.089877706+02:00","Elapsed":2371276960,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DLEBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"DLGBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAABAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAYABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.165701815+02:00","Elapsed":75934549,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UH0BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"UH2BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.169195916+02:00","Elapsed":5448632294,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UH0BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"UH2BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.218814074+02:00","Elapsed":4491154777,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3e8BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"3e+BgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMdHAC4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMcFGi4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMfUAC4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.457586549+02:00","Elapsed":90966164,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wpEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"wpGBgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAAEwAECABBQAAqQAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAAEwAECABBQAAEwAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAAEwAECABBQAAMQAAAAAAAAAAAEY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:04.473701027+02:00","Elapsed":101707863,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dY4BAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"dY6BgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAAODwAE2BKoEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:23.802908867+02:00","Elapsed":203264101,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"azsBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"azuBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAHBwA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:23.864400634+02:00","Elapsed":49339701,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OoUBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"OoWBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAAODwAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:23.918708324+02:00","Elapsed":51034969,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yX8BAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"yX+BgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAAOCgAE2BKoEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:29.70357105+02:00","Elapsed":192228,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n6wBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"n6yBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAHAgA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:29.726501993+02:00","Elapsed":205153,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1/UBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"1/WBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAAOCgAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:35:29.733543931+02:00","Elapsed":216409,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PtoBAAABAAAAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"PtqBgAABAAYAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEKdGltZS1tYWNvcwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAHcAGAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/SJ9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9NH0IdGltZS1vc3gBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdwAEEf02fQh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/TT9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9Nv0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:06.89628282+02:00","Elapsed":248583227,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rFIBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"rFKBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAYAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAYABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:33.345170384+02:00","Elapsed":185211476,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kuUBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"kuWBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:33.486347833+02:00","Elapsed":326373383,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kuUBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"kuWBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:33.664437305+02:00","Elapsed":129295049,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HGgBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"HGiBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:55.608060589+02:00","Elapsed":18783208092,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HGgBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"HGiBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:55.61163215+02:00","Elapsed":21800781997,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HGgBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"HGiBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:36:55.662340832+02:00","Elapsed":20821128701,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TV0BAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"TV2BgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAANhwAE2BKoEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:37:40.059734778+02:00","Elapsed":243893,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/UYBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"/UaBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAGfwA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:37:40.063994391+02:00","Elapsed":193090,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IPoBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"IPqBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAANhwAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:37:40.067512984+02:00","Elapsed":196127,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xQYBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"xQaBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAANVAAE2BKoEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:31.725074891+02:00","Elapsed":485294,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v9wBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"v9yBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAGTAA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:31.742998571+02:00","Elapsed":227567,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m8QBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"m8SBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAANVAAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:31.758731142+02:00","Elapsed":169991,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fggBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dw5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"fgiBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dw5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cOcG9ybmh1YnByZW1pdW0DY29tAAAFAAEAAA4PABQOcG9ybmh1YnByZW1pdW0DY29tAA5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQAADg8ABNgSqBM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:36.453816373+02:00","Elapsed":281519066,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wcYBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"wcaBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAGRwA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:36.458852353+02:00","Elapsed":162932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lqYBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"lqaBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAANTwAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:38:36.467231825+02:00","Elapsed":155717,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JWMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dw5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"JWOBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dw5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cOcG9ybmh1YnByZW1pdW0DY29tAAAFAAEAAA3CABQOcG9ybmh1YnByZW1pdW0DY29tAA5wb3JuaHVicHJlbWl1bQNjb20AAAEAAQAADcIABNgSqBM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:53.857025458+02:00","Elapsed":225159,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DmwBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"DmyBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAF+gA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:53.860055401+02:00","Elapsed":216384,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yGQBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"yGSBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAANAgAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:53.863603968+02:00","Elapsed":165030,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG8BAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"GG+BgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAANAAAE2BKoEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:55.604081905+02:00","Elapsed":252021,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cuYBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"cuaBgAABAAAAAQAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAF+AA6A25zMQlzd2lmdHdpbGwDY29tAANkbnMJc3dpZnR3aWxsA2NvbQB4C44fAABwgAAAHCAAEnUAAACowA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:55.615646709+02:00","Elapsed":206912,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3EgBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"3EiBgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwABAAANAAAgAAoLc210cC1zY2FuMDECbXgJcmVmbGVjdGVkA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:39:55.65326053+02:00","Elapsed":187217,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wDgBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wDiBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEPZm9yY2VzYWZlc2VhcmNoBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.493990044+02:00","Elapsed":4256932208,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"teIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"teKFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.494146199+02:00","Elapsed":4257165616,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nqUBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"nqWBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEPZm9yY2VzYWZlc2VhcmNoBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAABicABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.494650973+02:00","Elapsed":2249771019,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"teIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"teKFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAABicABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.494783299+02:00","Elapsed":2249983450,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tzYBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"tzaBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEPZm9yY2VzYWZlc2VhcmNoBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.497364255+02:00","Elapsed":5259059597,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"teIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"teKFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:31.497491047+02:00","Elapsed":5259261863,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uE8BAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"uE+BgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOm4Zgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpuGQHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6bhxB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOm4ZQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpuIoHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6biL","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.172865545+02:00","Elapsed":91242009,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pX0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"pX2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdgAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.473792998+02:00","Elapsed":89200450,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"S7gBAAABAAAAAAAADmVuY3J5cHRlZC10Ym4wB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"S7iBgAABAAYAAAAADmVuY3J5cHRlZC10Ym4wB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuIoOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuGQOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuHEOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuGUOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuGYOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAIsABEDpuIs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.656904701+02:00","Elapsed":126737756,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8CMBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"8COBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADg8ABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.704391545+02:00","Elapsed":117581,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"I1kBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"I1mFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQN3d3cGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAABAAEAAA4PAATY7yZ4","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.704542057+02:00","Elapsed":318524,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zE0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"zE2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAggAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:32.900504598+02:00","Elapsed":71620283,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7e4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"7e6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAABKwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:33.140773689+02:00","Elapsed":110907671,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5sMBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"5sOBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAEcAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEcABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEcABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEcABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEcABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:33.674604043+02:00","Elapsed":84357727,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F3cBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"F3eBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAErABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6aeaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6aedCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6aebCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6aec","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:33.963306085+02:00","Elapsed":67891537,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gHQBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"gHSFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:40:34.24721763+02:00","Elapsed":286355,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iLcBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"iLeBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAABUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAABUABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:40.233194941+02:00","Elapsed":133222742,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D9gBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"D9iBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:40.388228659+02:00","Elapsed":286848933,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D9gBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"D9iBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:40.424965895+02:00","Elapsed":184408240,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xpcBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"xpeBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:40.729759249+02:00","Elapsed":64954580,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AfcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AfeBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAlgAEQOmnXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:54.729642991+02:00","Elapsed":152781003,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"b2QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"b2SBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAxgAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:55.089920591+02:00","Elapsed":39225624,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/jABAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"/jCBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAN8AHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAN8ABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAN8ABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAN8ABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAN8ABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:56.034335954+02:00","Elapsed":38215751,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RfkBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"RfmFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:45:56.437247684+02:00","Elapsed":276738,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QScBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QSeFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:46:12.553180814+02:00","Elapsed":481581,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:46:12.635339868+02:00","Elapsed":274177,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Pm4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"Pm6FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:46:12.638137003+02:00","Elapsed":206516,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x7ABAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"x7CBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:46:12.76612744+02:00","Elapsed":213398327,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.464868916+02:00","Elapsed":59390929696,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s5WBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABEwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABEwAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABEwAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABEwAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABEwAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABEwAEQOmmXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.535976075+02:00","Elapsed":59006652899,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s5WBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAtgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAtgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAtgAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAtgAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAtgAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.578515974+02:00","Elapsed":52045223796,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s5WBgAABAAcAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAJQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAESn1HXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJQAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.578574666+02:00","Elapsed":44043507474,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s5WBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAApwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAApwAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAApwAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAApwAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAApwAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.580436162+02:00","Elapsed":56052359134,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s5WBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAqwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.580550673+02:00","Elapsed":58032943415,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wAoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wAqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.589550515+02:00","Elapsed":44054547513,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZFMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZFOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.58967408+02:00","Elapsed":59060382342,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wAoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wAqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.589744576+02:00","Elapsed":58037046568,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wAoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wAqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.589825701+02:00","Elapsed":56057785785,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wAoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wAqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.589935474+02:00","Elapsed":59060634640,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nhQBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"nhSBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.591037973+02:00","Elapsed":52058219852,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nhQBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"nhSBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.591156777+02:00","Elapsed":56063068597,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wAoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wAqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.593236085+02:00","Elapsed":52059945491,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nhQBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"nhSBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.597757354+02:00","Elapsed":58069826560,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nhQBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"nhSBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.597834007+02:00","Elapsed":44063117627,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nhQBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"nhSBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.603260963+02:00","Elapsed":59077004718,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZFMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZFOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.638160842+02:00","Elapsed":58090466740,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZFMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZFOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.660853176+02:00","Elapsed":56132745285,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZFMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZFOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.660993283+02:00","Elapsed":52127678778,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.661102315+02:00","Elapsed":51580814297,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZFMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZFOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.661161591+02:00","Elapsed":44126121277,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.661452773+02:00","Elapsed":3574750008,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.6787867+02:00","Elapsed":66617092791,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.678901545+02:00","Elapsed":65606097365,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.678963117+02:00","Elapsed":63602362006,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KvQBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KvSBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.678990184+02:00","Elapsed":35597727397,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HAYBAAABAAAAAAAAAzE4MgMyNTIDMTY5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQ==","Answer":"HAaBgwABAAAAAQAAAzE4MgMyNTIDMTY5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQMxOTMHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAGAAEAAAcBADgDcHJpB2F1dGhkbnMEcmlwZQNuZXQAA2RucwRyaXBlA25ldABb3c95AAAOEAAAAlgADS8AAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.722148974+02:00","Elapsed":95628068244,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HAYBAAABAAAAAAAAAzE4MgMyNTIDMTY5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQ==","Answer":"HAaBgwABAAAAAQAAAzE4MgMyNTIDMTY5AzE5Mwdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQMxOTMHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAGAAEAAAb/ADgDcHJpB2F1dGhkbnMEcmlwZQNuZXQAA2RucwRyaXBlA25ldABb3c95AAAOEAAAAlgADS8AAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.722278994+02:00","Elapsed":100636238762,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GTABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"GTCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAODwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADg8ABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4PAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAODwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.94970554+02:00","Elapsed":136168730,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tvQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"tvSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABvABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABvAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABvAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABvAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABvAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABvAARKfYVf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.949787685+02:00","Elapsed":136208182,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"o3sBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"o3uBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAACNAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.987023761+02:00","Elapsed":110870803,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X1QBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoMxFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"X1SBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoMxFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDMRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAABvACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAAG8ABEp9hYQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:10.987131465+02:00","Elapsed":112892460,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Mg0BAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Mg2FgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:11.482848711+02:00","Elapsed":553972,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"a8IBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"a8KFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:11.483007331+02:00","Elapsed":693018,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RbgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"RbiBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAC4ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC4AAStwkycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC4AAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC4AAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC4AAStwkyd","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:11.558192709+02:00","Elapsed":85600795,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lYIBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"lYKBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAHABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAHAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:11.562103402+02:00","Elapsed":79831637,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JnABAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"JnCFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:12.321679363+02:00","Elapsed":295356,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KowBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KoyFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:47:13.613216619+02:00","Elapsed":227885,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ZkBAAABAAAAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4ZmBgAABAAQAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAABAAEAAAEcAATQSdOlBmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQAAARwABNBJ0soGYXNkYXNkA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHAAE0EnS2QZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAABAAEAAAEcAATQSdOx","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:51:32.060478174+02:00","Elapsed":344817703,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+zoBAAABAAAAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AABwAAQ==","Answer":"+zqBgAABAAAAAQAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AABwAAQZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAAGAAEAAACiAEkDbnMxDWRzcmVkaXJlY3Rpb24DY29tAApob3N0bWFzdGVyDWRvbWFpbnNwb25zb3IDY29tAHgNC8UAAA4QAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:51:32.105170515+02:00","Elapsed":40908842,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GIABAAABAAAAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"GICBgAABAAAAAQAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAA8AAQZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAAGAAEAAABcAEkDbnMxDWRzcmVkaXJlY3Rpb24DY29tAApob3N0bWFzdGVyDWRvbWFpbnNwb25zb3IDY29tAHgNC8UAAA4QAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:51:32.165853646+02:00","Elapsed":57638220,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ZkBAAABAAAAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4ZmBgAABAAQAAAAABmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAATQSdOxBmFzZGFzZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABNBJ0soGYXNkYXNkA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE0EnTpQZhc2Rhc2QDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAATQSdLZ","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:51:32.167898286+02:00","Elapsed":5461048354,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JW8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"JW+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:53:27.980708433+02:00","Elapsed":289177,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RPgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RPiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:53:27.982575609+02:00","Elapsed":215878,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MAMBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"MAOBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:53:28.037134432+02:00","Elapsed":156126014,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pN8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"pN+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:53:28.085294209+02:00","Elapsed":266986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n3QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"n3SBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABFgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFgAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFgAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFgAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.186338558+02:00","Elapsed":42299962033,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NlQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NlSBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.196284233+02:00","Elapsed":44318530068,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xwsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"xwuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.196517245+02:00","Elapsed":45317850214,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ig4BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"ig6BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.196557507+02:00","Elapsed":45323534448,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NlQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NlSBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.196601308+02:00","Elapsed":45319106060,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n3QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"n3SBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA4QAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA4QAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA4QAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA4QAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA4QAEQOmnXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.199156561+02:00","Elapsed":38317755781,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ig4BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"ig6BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.199337424+02:00","Elapsed":30315394802,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n3QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"n3SBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQOmmXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.199376248+02:00","Elapsed":45320714174,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ig4BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"ig6BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.199430483+02:00","Elapsed":44321921625,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n3QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"n3SBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABHQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.199470425+02:00","Elapsed":44321720556,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NlQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NlSBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.209908059+02:00","Elapsed":42323523506,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ig4BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"ig6BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.209990334+02:00","Elapsed":42326573685,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NlQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NlSBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.210088004+02:00","Elapsed":38328691038,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ig4BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"ig6BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.258768262+02:00","Elapsed":38377362479,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EgsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EguBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ20PFV","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.258930586+02:00","Elapsed":44377061674,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EgsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EguBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQixVQB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.25903877+02:00","Elapsed":43368958810,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EgsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EguBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.259141978+02:00","Elapsed":37368787011,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xwsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"xwuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.25925969+02:00","Elapsed":44381496129,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xwsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"xwuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.25927724+02:00","Elapsed":30375010541,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xwsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"xwuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.259363218+02:00","Elapsed":38377926901,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"n3QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"n3SBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAgAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgAAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgAAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgAAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgAAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.259449773+02:00","Elapsed":30375170350,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NlQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"NlSBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.25951594+02:00","Elapsed":30375020595,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EgsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EguBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQixVQB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.259575363+02:00","Elapsed":41373537095,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EgsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EguBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.259635987+02:00","Elapsed":29362936933,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xwsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"xwuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:12.311324532+02:00","Elapsed":42424902372,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uzgBAAABAAAAAAAAAWIHX2Rucy1zZARfdWRwATABMgMxMDACMTAHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAE=","Answer":"uziBgwABAAAAAAAAAWIHX2Rucy1zZARfdWRwATABMgMxMDACMTAHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:36.038625046+02:00","Elapsed":208809648,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"I58BAAABAAAAAAAAAmRiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"I5+BgwABAAAAAAAAAmRiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:36.04584255+02:00","Elapsed":210403965,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xKIBAAABAAAAAAAAAWIHX2Rucy1zZARfdWRwATABMgMxMDACMTAHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAE=","Answer":"xKKBgwABAAAAAAAAAWIHX2Rucy1zZARfdWRwATABMgMxMDACMTAHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:36.050732009+02:00","Elapsed":215223689,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eLsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmRiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"eLuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmRiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:54:36.050873391+02:00","Elapsed":219153792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"d5wBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"d5yBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA6gAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:14.030907932+02:00","Elapsed":204041648,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F5gBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"F5iBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMcQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIsHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxmB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZAdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTGUHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkyK","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:14.218518545+02:00","Elapsed":108830290,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"y5sBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"y5uBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA8QAEQOmnXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:14.570431878+02:00","Elapsed":87724849,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C14BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"C16BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAeQATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4ZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4cQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4ZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4iwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4ZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAeQAEQOm4ig==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:15.016207237+02:00","Elapsed":53325704,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZwsBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ZwuBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAIEAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAIEABK3CTJoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAIEABK3CTJwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAIEABK3CTJsIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAIEABK3CTJ0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:15.468110934+02:00","Elapsed":42946666,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pwIBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"pwKBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAADRABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADRAAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADRAAStwkycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADRAAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADRAAStwkyb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:15.796647995+02:00","Elapsed":52242462,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxJweXRob25mb3JiZWdpbm5lcnMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjqBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dxJweXRob25mb3JiZWdpbm5lcnMDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3EnB5dGhvbmZvcmJlZ2lubmVycwNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDQYZaoDd3d3EnB5dGhvbmZvcmJlZ2lubmVycwNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDaVYEc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:16.14057013+02:00","Elapsed":233304194,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BdYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dw50dXRvcmlhbHNwb2ludANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BdaBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dw50dXRvcmlhbHNwb2ludANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cOdHV0b3JpYWxzcG9pbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAKmABoCczIDZ3AxA3dhYwlsYW1iZGFjZG4DbmV0AAJzMgNncDEDd2FjCWxhbWJkYWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAqYABF243Co=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:36.964552869+02:00","Elapsed":294130069,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4yABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4yCFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:37.39183333+02:00","Elapsed":239387,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EUQBAAABAAAAAAAAB3BhZ2VhZDIRZ29vZ2xlc3luZGljYXRpb24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EUSBgAABAAUAAAAAB3BhZ2VhZDIRZ29vZ2xlc3luZGljYXRpb24DY29tAAABAAEHcGFnZWFkMhFnb29nbGVzeW5kaWNhdGlvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAAI8AHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAI8ABEDpppwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAI8ABEDpppoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAI8ABEDppp0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAI8ABEDppps=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:37.494320926+02:00","Elapsed":103421896,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6gIBAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"6gKBgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAOAAGwxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAADgAARCZgFe","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:37.963130384+02:00","Elapsed":134665553,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uS4BAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"uS6FgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:38.086974306+02:00","Elapsed":305529,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rTIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl3M3NjaG9vbHMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"rTKBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwl3M3NjaG9vbHMDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXczc2Nob29scwNjb20AAAUAAQAADg8AGwVjczgzNwN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AAVjczgzNwN3YWMLZWRnZWNhc3RjZG4DbmV0AAABAAEAAA4PAATA5YXd","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:50.233332166+02:00","Elapsed":584990155,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4/kBAAABAAAAAAAABnN0YXRpYwVoLWJpZANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4/mFgwABAAAAAQAABnN0YXRpYwVoLWJpZANjb20AAAEAAQZzdGF0aWMFaC1iaWQDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFgZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgZzdGF0aWMFaC1iaWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||h-bid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:50.831810477+02:00","Elapsed":337328,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gh0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gh2BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAC2ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC2AARKfYWdCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC2AARKfYWaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC2AARKfYWbCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC2AARKfYWc","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:50.967428418+02:00","Elapsed":96846411,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3CwBAAABAAAAAAAACXRyYW5zbGF0ZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"3CyBgAABAAcAAAAACXRyYW5zbGF0ZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJdHJhbnNsYXRlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAI8AEwR3d3czAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hWQEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hWYEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hYoEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hYsEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hWUEd3d3MwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAI8ABEp9hXE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:51.139672772+02:00","Elapsed":308255551,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J4UBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NzZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"J4WBgAABAAYAAAAAA2NzZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp4oDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp3EDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2UDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp4sDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2QDY3NlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2Y=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:51.246261151+02:00","Elapsed":107450077,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hMEBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"hMGFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:51.277208902+02:00","Elapsed":185978,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5u4BAAABAAAAAAAACXRyYW5zbGF0ZQpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"5u6BgAABAAEAAAAACXRyYW5zbGF0ZQpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABCXRyYW5zbGF0ZQpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAALwAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:51.497416398+02:00","Elapsed":94153638,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zmUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"zmWBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHQAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHQAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHQAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:52.002629854+02:00","Elapsed":200442,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8icBAAABAAAAAAAACGNsaWVudHMxBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8ieBgAABAAcAAAAACGNsaWVudHMxBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQhjbGllbnRzMQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAErABYHY2xpZW50cwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6admB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6aeLB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adxB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adlB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6aeKB2NsaWVudHMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adk","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:55:52.131241991+02:00","Elapsed":89181994,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3BYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"3BaBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAgZAAS53Lj/","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:40.774327545+02:00","Elapsed":136274,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/6QBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"/6SBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAgZAAS53Lj/","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:40.774417561+02:00","Elapsed":74620,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"B+ABAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"B+CFgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAACBkABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:40.774496872+02:00","Elapsed":60124063,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"B+ABAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"B+CFgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAACBkABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:40.774536104+02:00","Elapsed":5062733577,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yQkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"yQmBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:41.025916738+02:00","Elapsed":246393938,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2GIBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"2GKFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:41.02606055+02:00","Elapsed":246599921,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6QABAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"6QCBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:41.126340906+02:00","Elapsed":95674163,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yR4BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"yR6FgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T20:58:41.126501457+02:00","Elapsed":95912375,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xVgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"xViBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQgdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Q==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:19.140572155+02:00","Elapsed":284453580,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qlQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"qlSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:19.43003628+02:00","Elapsed":57522377,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/VIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"/VKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:20.171612805+02:00","Elapsed":73587392,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ruUBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ruWBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAABJwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMiw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:21.376879945+02:00","Elapsed":40502910,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"aZIBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"aZKBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:21.5856828+02:00","Elapsed":90710227,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Zq8BAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Zq+BgAABAAUAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAErABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.001593277+02:00","Elapsed":53740441,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3+gBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"3+iBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAErACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGSLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB4iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAcIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQHSLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAbIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQASPALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB8iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAAI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGCLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEAIjwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBADIw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.079856603+02:00","Elapsed":111091809,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DDoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"DDqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAEAAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.135237874+02:00","Elapsed":43712800,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"d6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"d6GBgAABAAUAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNyYXcRZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABcGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2WAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwIU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.23444587+02:00","Elapsed":232929243,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rlYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rlaFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.411092899+02:00","Elapsed":268684,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZQEBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ZQGFgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.413191993+02:00","Elapsed":223187,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tzsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"tzuBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEWABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEWAARA6biaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEWAARA6bicCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEWAARA6bidCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEWAARA6bib","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.445648014+02:00","Elapsed":42537902,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"W2cBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"W2eBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXORMX","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:22.455167304+02:00","Elapsed":42195615,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YMYBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"YMaFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:23.28368512+02:00","Elapsed":328533,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jAgBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"jAiBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAQoAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQoABEp9hZ0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQoABEp9hZoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQoABEp9hZsIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQoABEp9hZw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:23.322353937+02:00","Elapsed":38918105,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TNMBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TNOBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAErABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+cCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+a","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:23.323534422+02:00","Elapsed":40199085,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jrsBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"jruFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:24.573619798+02:00","Elapsed":292755,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9MMBAAABAAAAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"9MOBgAABAAIAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQVkZW1vcwl3aXJlZGRvdHMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA7AA8Jd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAJd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEIs4M1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:24.833343513+02:00","Elapsed":128046201,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8OABAAABAAAAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8OCBgAABAAEAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQl3aXJlZGRvdHMObWV0YWxvZ2ljc3NvZnQDY29tAAABAAEAAASvAAREQXpn","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:27.206452414+02:00","Elapsed":137827091,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lk4BAAABAAAAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"lk6BgAABAAIAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABCGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABAAABKwAEaBh6UQhjc2VydmljZQh1bmRlcm5ldANvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYe1E=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:33.131280305+02:00","Elapsed":131235130,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kH4BAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"kH6BgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAABJABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAEkABK3CzV4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:36.095474039+02:00","Elapsed":210631800,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1SQBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"1SSFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:37.379508438+02:00","Elapsed":276542,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bZwBAAABAAAAAAAABmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"bZyBgAABAAIAAAAABmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAHv1xBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:43.123221663+02:00","Elapsed":205474896,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F5ABAAABAAAAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"F5CBgAABAAUAAAAACmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAAAQABCmFzc2V0cy1jZG4GZ2l0aHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:44.786303473+02:00","Elapsed":135550646,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bGwBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"bGyBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMyEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:44.909596621+02:00","Elapsed":252795214,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j6oBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"j6qBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMxEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:44.911899621+02:00","Elapsed":255090853,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4U4BAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4U6BgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMwEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:44.940028689+02:00","Elapsed":283244743,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rOQBAAABAAAAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rOSBgAABAAUAAAAACGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABCGF2YXRhcnMzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:44.940067339+02:00","Elapsed":141434842,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ay8BAAABAAAAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ay+BgAABAAUAAAAAC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAAAQABC3VzZXItaW1hZ2VzEWdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHAAXBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAcAASXZQCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHAAEl2VAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAABwABJdlgIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAcAASXZcCF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:45.77192775+02:00","Elapsed":126373650,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXQBAAABAAAAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XXSBgAABAAIAAAAADGdpdGh1Yi1jbG91ZAJzMwlhbWF6b25hd3MDY29tAAABAAEMZ2l0aHViLWNsb3VkAnMzCWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFgZzMy0xLXcJYW1hem9uYXdzA2NvbQAGczMtMS13CWFtYXpvbmF3cwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAAUABDTYEsg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:45.817022339+02:00","Elapsed":169214635,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eEMBAAABAAAAAAAACWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"eEOFgwABAAAAAQAACWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABAAEJY29sbGVjdG9yCWdpdGh1YmFwcANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAXxlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyCWNvbGxlY3RvcglnaXRodWJhcHADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||collector.githubapp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:45.85751954+02:00","Elapsed":251736,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VTABAAABAAAAAAAAA2FwaQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"VTCBgAABAAIAAAAAA2FwaQZnaXRodWIDY29tAAABAAEDYXBpBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XQDYXBpBmdpdGh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAe/XU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:00:46.112178822+02:00","Elapsed":77741501,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7I4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZyZWRkaXQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"7I6BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwZyZWRkaXQDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BnJlZGRpdANjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFwZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAABQAEl2UBjAZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABJdlQYwGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAASXZYGMBnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAABQAEl2XBjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:05.186981872+02:00","Elapsed":187748410,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C/cBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwxyZWRkaXRzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"C/eBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwxyZWRkaXRzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3DHJlZGRpdHN0YXRpYwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAB0AFwZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2UBjAZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlQYwGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZYGMBnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2XBjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:06.672588508+02:00","Elapsed":84421699,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0pIBAAABAAAAAAAAAWMPYW1hem9uLWFkc3lzdGVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"0pKFgwABAAAAAQAAAWMPYW1hem9uLWFkc3lzdGVtA2NvbQAAAQABAWMPYW1hem9uLWFkc3lzdGVtA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIBYw9hbWF6b24tYWRzeXN0ZW0DY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||amazon-adsystem.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:10.665492676+02:00","Elapsed":211741,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uXwBAAABAAAAAAAAAWMGYWF4YWRzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"uXyFgwABAAAAAQAAAWMGYWF4YWRzA2NvbQAAAQABAWMGYWF4YWRzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIBYwZhYXhhZHMDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||aaxads.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:10.667688412+02:00","Elapsed":177124,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GykBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtyZWRkaXRtZWRpYQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GymBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwtyZWRkaXRtZWRpYQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLcmVkZGl0bWVkaWEDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABcGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAYwGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUGMBnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2WBjAZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwYw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:13.192335355+02:00","Elapsed":120074325,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ucIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGV0YWdtYW5hZ2VyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ucKBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGV0YWdtYW5hZ2VyA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGV0YWdtYW5hZ2VyA2NvbQAABQABAAAA8wAjFHd3dy1nb29nbGV0YWdtYW5hZ2VyAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAUd3d3LWdvb2dsZXRhZ21hbmFnZXIBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAADzAARssQ9h","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:14.858651947+02:00","Elapsed":67317152,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"sakBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBXJsY2RuA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"samFgwABAAAAAQAAAmlkBXJsY2RuA2NvbQAAAQABAmlkBXJsY2RuA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXICaWQFcmxjZG4DY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||rlcdn.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:15.259917407+02:00","Elapsed":457529,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"StIBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"StKBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAACAAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAIABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAIAAQXORMX","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:15.34296228+02:00","Elapsed":59876995,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VkYBAAABAAAAAAAAB2dhdGV3YXkGcmVkZGl0A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"VkaBgAABAAUAAAAAB2dhdGV3YXkGcmVkZGl0A2NvbQAAAQABB2dhdGV3YXkGcmVkZGl0A2NvbQAABQABAAAAHQAXBnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQGMBnJlZGRpdANtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2VBjAZyZWRkaXQDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgYwGcmVkZGl0A21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcGM","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:01:15.460671028+02:00","Elapsed":220471714,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9jEBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"9jGBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAARABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAARAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:02:32.310739727+02:00","Elapsed":255970643,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KekBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KemFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:02:34.230077531+02:00","Elapsed":254122,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D/8BAAABAAAAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"D/+BgAABAAYAAAAACnRpbWUtbWFjb3MFYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAEKdGltZS1tYWNvcwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAHcAGAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/SJ9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9NH0IdGltZS1vc3gBZwdhYXBsaW1nA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdwAEEf02fQh0aW1lLW9zeAFnB2FhcGxpbWcDY29tAAABAAEAAAB3AAQR/TT9CHRpbWUtb3N4AWcHYWFwbGltZwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAHcABBH9Nv0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:02:57.34880905+02:00","Elapsed":216667376,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lYQBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"lYSFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:03:06.035452718+02:00","Elapsed":279424,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"q0sBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"q0uFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:04:13.34539059+02:00","Elapsed":314001,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D2YBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"D2aFgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:04:13.345893567+02:00","Elapsed":246308,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qkIBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"qkKFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:04:13.395521832+02:00","Elapsed":332855,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dzEBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"dzGBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAFABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:04:13.600864624+02:00","Elapsed":205618941,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J+0BAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"J+2FgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:04:15.515618355+02:00","Elapsed":269693,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9X8BAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"9X+FgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:29.300791078+02:00","Elapsed":333210,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P6MBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"P6OBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:48.444413672+02:00","Elapsed":161923595,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BKEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BKGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:49.304111629+02:00","Elapsed":327008,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x7ABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"x7CBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ20PFV","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:49.446651945+02:00","Elapsed":50228025,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"69ABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"69CFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:49.603737413+02:00","Elapsed":192598,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VJcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"VJeFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:49.705119925+02:00","Elapsed":265237,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VY8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"VY+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:05:49.917472549+02:00","Elapsed":281796,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oWEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"oWGBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAwQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwQAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:56.872341807+02:00","Elapsed":272580134,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"C5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.047023637+02:00","Elapsed":264460321,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WqQBAAABAAAAAAAABnJlZGRpdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WqSBgAABAAQAAAAABnJlZGRpdANjb20AAAEAAQZyZWRkaXQDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZQGMBnJlZGRpdANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwYwGcmVkZGl0A2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEl2VBjAZyZWRkaXQDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZYGM","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.200306035+02:00","Elapsed":153411078,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eVQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"eVSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.254614523+02:00","Elapsed":207704246,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wlMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wlOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMwAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADMABMAAUPICbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAATAAFDv","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.310187692+02:00","Elapsed":51613604,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EKcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"EKeFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.341648263+02:00","Elapsed":219427,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Qt0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Qt2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.341728305+02:00","Elapsed":306867,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yZMBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"yZOBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:06:57.480400139+02:00","Elapsed":139283491,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"XXyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:07:03.524998521+02:00","Elapsed":60356039,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"c8iBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:07:03.537753739+02:00","Elapsed":70583718,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OCcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OCeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.663771516+02:00","Elapsed":169379056468,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OCcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OCeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.676949991+02:00","Elapsed":171391211274,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OCcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OCeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.677060528+02:00","Elapsed":172394532346,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OCcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OCeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.67823711+02:00","Elapsed":165389932034,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OCcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OCeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.679030422+02:00","Elapsed":157378126672,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PYeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.679879086+02:00","Elapsed":141201283595,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PYeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.681516132+02:00","Elapsed":134192529572,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PYeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.681587712+02:00","Elapsed":140200818695,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PYeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.681985031+02:00","Elapsed":138196832364,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PYcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PYeBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.686027059+02:00","Elapsed":126197145169,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oWEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"oWGBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.686506894+02:00","Elapsed":111117436412,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"HBGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.830033618+02:00","Elapsed":172547530964,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"HBGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.835762177+02:00","Elapsed":169551358073,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.837057172+02:00","Elapsed":139480351721,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"E6GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.84437648+02:00","Elapsed":165556088230,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"E6GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.850280588+02:00","Elapsed":157547608931,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"E6GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.850347398+02:00","Elapsed":172567860704,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.854848831+02:00","Elapsed":127493175176,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"E6GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.855054799+02:00","Elapsed":169570412010,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.855120221+02:00","Elapsed":141500919581,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IOsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IOuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.85517565+02:00","Elapsed":139498463280,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.855219141+02:00","Elapsed":142502787752,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"HBGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.855274504+02:00","Elapsed":171569571832,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IOsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IOuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.855320661+02:00","Elapsed":142500094986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E6EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"E6GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.85536078+02:00","Elapsed":171569651051,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IOsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IOuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.86133857+02:00","Elapsed":141504059922,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"XXyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.903864968+02:00","Elapsed":112446494571,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IOsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IOuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904078133+02:00","Elapsed":127541659321,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RYMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"RYOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904143455+02:00","Elapsed":135545459018,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"XXyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904246339+02:00","Elapsed":111456099008,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"HBGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904276368+02:00","Elapsed":165615977562,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IOsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IOuBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.90431142+02:00","Elapsed":135543235187,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"c8iBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904363561+02:00","Elapsed":111454063486,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HBEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"HBGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.904448719+02:00","Elapsed":157612079982,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"c8iBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:40.9045119+02:00","Elapsed":112431646601,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oWEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"oWGBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.168736935+02:00","Elapsed":110598075498,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"XXyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.168940262+02:00","Elapsed":109716708776,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"c8iBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.173223433+02:00","Elapsed":109704902525,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oWEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"oWGBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWQAESn2MXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.175970601+02:00","Elapsed":108604138470,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"c8iBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.176609058+02:00","Elapsed":105713806627,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XXwBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"XXyBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.176894907+02:00","Elapsed":105720740978,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rCSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.268046764+02:00","Elapsed":170949246415,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ecEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ecGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.268705995+02:00","Elapsed":171969882657,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ecEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ecGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.268934465+02:00","Elapsed":168966878289,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"an0BAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"an2BgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADakABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADakABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADakABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADakABLncuAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.270741007+02:00","Elapsed":169851137964,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rCSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.270942222+02:00","Elapsed":171967177522,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ecEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ecGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.271409556+02:00","Elapsed":164971604284,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rCSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.271649284+02:00","Elapsed":168960724745,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ecEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ecGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.274416416+02:00","Elapsed":170955982301,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rCSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.276977926+02:00","Elapsed":164977228343,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ecEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ecGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.277361962+02:00","Elapsed":156973948117,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rCSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.287869811+02:00","Elapsed":156984454223,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XqIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XqKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.288036293+02:00","Elapsed":141706030527,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XqIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XqKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.288519402+02:00","Elapsed":140701505898,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Uj0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Uj2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.299682427+02:00","Elapsed":141920592512,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XqIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XqKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.305867726+02:00","Elapsed":138716247494,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XqIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XqKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.3059668+02:00","Elapsed":134713279929,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Uj0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Uj2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.306236957+02:00","Elapsed":138922174243,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QQMBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QQOBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAArAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.312787764+02:00","Elapsed":172009003344,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QQMBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QQOBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAA5AAQ0XuYs","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.312881611+02:00","Elapsed":170993778309,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QQMBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QQOBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAIAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.312959523+02:00","Elapsed":169002023612,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.31308673+02:00","Elapsed":169995998558,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Uj0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Uj2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.313094441+02:00","Elapsed":140929453927,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Uj0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Uj2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.313224445+02:00","Elapsed":126922459926,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Uj0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Uj2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.313358302+02:00","Elapsed":134915864202,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+MBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Y+OBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.320642255+02:00","Elapsed":168682648800,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.320760426+02:00","Elapsed":169014754577,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+MBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Y+OBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.320848788+02:00","Elapsed":169697586991,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XqIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XqKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.321462105+02:00","Elapsed":126726382005,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKgBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WKiBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.321857273+02:00","Elapsed":122462469448,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAIAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.322057838+02:00","Elapsed":110933862475,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"C5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.322228508+02:00","Elapsed":110543269921,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eVQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"eVSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.322405546+02:00","Elapsed":107325433129,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"C5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.322591437+02:00","Elapsed":111547709020,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.329688991+02:00","Elapsed":172025933636,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.329777192+02:00","Elapsed":171010985419,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+MBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Y+OBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAABGAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAEYABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.329814202+02:00","Elapsed":162693511807,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fsABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"fsCBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.32990265+02:00","Elapsed":170012091117,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"C5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADagABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.33013949+02:00","Elapsed":108550537617,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eVQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"eVSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAwwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.330394452+02:00","Elapsed":106221605060,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.339790512+02:00","Elapsed":165039995107,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAmAAQ27xDb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.339964993+02:00","Elapsed":141962511411,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+MBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Y+OBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.340075243+02:00","Elapsed":166703103238,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAOAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.340128968+02:00","Elapsed":140959251987,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.348996454+02:00","Elapsed":157045214440,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAOAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.349054987+02:00","Elapsed":126961907756,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+MBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Y+OBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.34909242+02:00","Elapsed":154710156632,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAIAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.349125116+02:00","Elapsed":138967699796,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HDEBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"HDGBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAiAAQ27xDb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.349169663+02:00","Elapsed":134952576373,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QQMBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QQOBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0XuYs","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.349214213+02:00","Elapsed":165049410956,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P1gBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"P1iBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.349318028+02:00","Elapsed":141043943146,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKgBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WKiBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.352283859+02:00","Elapsed":137505747293,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKgBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WKiBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.363621726+02:00","Elapsed":130500191232,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKgBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WKiBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.366477874+02:00","Elapsed":134515940154,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"R7wBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"R7yBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIanVnZ2Nhc2gDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAATYEqhP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.372310653+02:00","Elapsed":141889180932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UigBAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"UiiBgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAADg8ABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.376963921+02:00","Elapsed":107505479052,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QQMBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QQOBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0XuYs","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.414205728+02:00","Elapsed":157110241312,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKgBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WKiBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:08:41.491571134+02:00","Elapsed":136646600792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"li8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"li+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAXgAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:17.806691407+02:00","Elapsed":165384562,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AkgBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AkiBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTGQHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkyKB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMiwdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTHEHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:18.034223872+02:00","Elapsed":63262226,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EIUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"EIWBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAACgAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:18.466678794+02:00","Elapsed":40952099,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"y3EBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"y3GBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAATgATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAATgAEbLEPZQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:18.871892744+02:00","Elapsed":57164477,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DE0BAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DE2BgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAOEAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAOEABK3CTJsIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAOEABK3CTJ0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAOEABK3CTJoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAOEABK3CTJw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:19.375428158+02:00","Elapsed":45555308,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s24BAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"s26BgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAErABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6bicCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6bibCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6biaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARA6bid","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:19.726455367+02:00","Elapsed":40009339,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"y0cBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"y0eBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFcXVvcmEDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABYFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZYECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcEC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:19.781314476+02:00","Elapsed":73768295,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"728BAAABAAAAAAAABHFzYnICZnMIcXVvcmFjZG4DbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"72+BgAABAAUAAAAABHFzYnICZnMIcXVvcmFjZG4DbmV0AAABAAEEcXNicgJmcwhxdW9yYWNkbgNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAB0AFgVxdW9yYQNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAQIFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlQQIFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlgQIFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwQI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:20.358490967+02:00","Elapsed":74672013,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IKoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3FzZgJmcwhxdW9yYWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IKqBgAABAAUAAAAAA3FzZgJmcwhxdW9yYWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQNxc2YCZnMIcXVvcmFjZG4DbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAdABYFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZYECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcEC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:20.72281106+02:00","Elapsed":87145636,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FRQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3FwaAJmcwhxdW9yYWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FRSBgAABAAUAAAAAA3FwaAJmcwhxdW9yYWNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQNxcGgCZnMIcXVvcmFjZG4DbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAdABYFcXVvcmEDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQABXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZQECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZYECBXF1b3JhA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZcEC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:20.78156378+02:00","Elapsed":87998370,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"02wBAAABAAAAAAAABWNkbmpzCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"02yBgAABAAUAAAAABWNkbmpzCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDY29tAAABAAEFY2RuanMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANEABGgTxZcFY2RuanMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANEABGgTxpcFY2RuanMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANEABGgTxJcFY2RuanMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANEABGgTx5cFY2RuanMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANEABGgTw5c=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:21.417329441+02:00","Elapsed":97638851,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ddEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ddGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:21.511271335+02:00","Elapsed":305419,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ni0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2Nvbm5lY3QIZmFjZWJvb2sDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"Ni2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2Nvbm5lY3QIZmFjZWJvb2sDbmV0AAABAAEHY29ubmVjdAhmYWNlYm9vawNuZXQAAAUAAQAAAC0AFwhzY29udGVudAJ4eAVmYmNkbgNuZXQACHNjb250ZW50Anh4BWZiY2RuA25ldAAAAQABAAAALQAEuTzYEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:21.600732309+02:00","Elapsed":89742257,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wnQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wnSBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAoAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAACgABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:22.177993429+02:00","Elapsed":109612842,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s9MBAAABAAAAAAAACHN0YXRpY3h4CGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s9OBgAABAAIAAAAACHN0YXRpY3h4CGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQABCHN0YXRpY3h4CGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAABQABAAAAIAAXCHNjb250ZW50Anh4BWZiY2RuA25ldAAIc2NvbnRlbnQCeHgFZmJjZG4DbmV0AAABAAEAAAAgAAQfDUsM","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:22.299783446+02:00","Elapsed":231398033,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vkQBAAABAAAAAAAACXRjaDQ3NjE2MQN0Y2gFcXVvcmEDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vkSBgAABAAcAAAAACXRjaDQ3NjE2MQN0Y2gFcXVvcmEDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAA7ADgdcXVvcmEtcHJvZC10Y2gtdnBjLTExMzYxNjU3MDcJdXMtZWFzdC0xA2VsYglhbWF6b25hd3PAIMA1AAEAAQAAADsABDQWmDTANQABAAEAAAA7AAQjrrdBwDUAAQABAAAAOwAENEhM48A1AAEAAQAAADsABDTIoMbANQABAAEAAAA7AAQ0Bs4UwDUAAQABAAAAOwAEIui64Q==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:22.617052553+02:00","Elapsed":146921924,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JM4BAAABAAAAAAAAA2xvZwVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"JM6FgwABAAAAAQAAA2xvZwVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQNsb2cFcXVvcmEDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFUZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgNsb2cFcXVvcmEDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||log.quora.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:23.231645605+02:00","Elapsed":276116,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DzcBAAABAAAAAAAACGFjY291bnRzBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"DzeBgAABAAEAAAAACGFjY291bnRzBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQhhY2NvdW50cwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAACvAAStwkxU","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:09:23.776109489+02:00","Elapsed":71588269,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SKkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NkbgtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"SKmBgAABAAMAAAAAA2NkbgtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQNjZG4LbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATACEDY2RuC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADY2RuC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAYBWUyMjAxAWcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUyMjAxAWcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAABMABF9k0HU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:30.201015322+02:00","Elapsed":195466512,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2/oBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2/qBgAABAAMAAAAABnNlY3VyZQtsaXZlY2hhdGluYwNjb20AAAEAAQZzZWN1cmULbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATACQGc2VjdXJlC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAGc2VjdXJlC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAaBWUyMjAxA2tzZApha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAFZTIyMDEDa3NkCmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiGa","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:30.656631024+02:00","Elapsed":100846263,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Rb0BAAABAAAAAAAACGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Rb2BgAABAAMAAAAACGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAAAQABCGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmCGFjY291bnRzC2xpdmVjaGF0aW5jA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAIYWNjb3VudHMLbGl2ZWNoYXRpbmMDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABgFZTIyMDEBYgpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAFZTIyMDEBYgpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEF9MIbA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:31.13663717+02:00","Elapsed":85109375,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z1ABAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"z1CBgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAUAAQAAANcAGwxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnb29nbGVhZGFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAADXAARssQ9f","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:32.540142432+02:00","Elapsed":70425254,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wtABAAABAAAAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wtCBgAABAAIAAAAABWZvbnRzB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEFZm9udHMHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAUAAQAAAMUAGwxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAxnc3RhdGljYWRzc2wBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAADFAAStwkxe","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:33.131565226+02:00","Elapsed":38312253,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pSIBAAABAAAAAAAACXRjaDQ3NjE2MQN0Y2gFcXVvcmEDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"pSKBgAABAAcAAAAACXRjaDQ3NjE2MQN0Y2gFcXVvcmEDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAA7ADgdcXVvcmEtcHJvZC10Y2gtdnBjLTExMzYxNjU3MDcJdXMtZWFzdC0xA2VsYglhbWF6b25hd3PAIMA1AAEAAQAAADsABDQWmDTANQABAAEAAAA7AAQ0Bs4UwDUAAQABAAAAOwAENMigxsA1AAEAAQAAADsABCLouuHANQABAAEAAAA7AAQjrrdBwDUAAQABAAAAOwAENEhM4w==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:10:40.741150636+02:00","Elapsed":83567434,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RdYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"RdaBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEAAAUyAAS53Lj/","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:03.814212783+02:00","Elapsed":195362176,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4mQBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"4mSFgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAABTIABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:03.814365844+02:00","Elapsed":265707827,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PVMBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"PVOBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:04.214449165+02:00","Elapsed":316702706,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lGgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"lGiFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:04.214606194+02:00","Elapsed":316943414,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/hkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"/hmBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:04.431161925+02:00","Elapsed":129236988,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7FUBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"7FWFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:04.431324112+02:00","Elapsed":129525392,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rroBAAABAAAAAAAACG1hc3RlcjE1CnRlYW12aWV3ZXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"rrqBgAABAAEAAAAACG1hc3RlcjE1CnRlYW12aWV3ZXIDY29tAAABAAEIbWFzdGVyMTUKdGVhbXZpZXdlcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABLm8IAU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:58.195774098+02:00","Elapsed":404097932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mi0BAAABAAAAAAAAD1JPLUJVQy1BTlgtUjAwMgp0ZWFtdmlld2VyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"mi2BgAABAAEAAAAAD1JPLUJVQy1BTlgtUjAwMgp0ZWFtdmlld2VyA2NvbQAAAQABD1JPLUJVQy1BTlgtUjAwMgp0ZWFtdmlld2VyA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEvKz+hQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:11:58.565008785+02:00","Elapsed":129310500,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VI8BAAABAAAAAAAAB3VkcHBpbmcKdGVhbXZpZXdlcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"VI+BgAABAAUAAAAAB3VkcHBpbmcKdGVhbXZpZXdlcgNjb20AAAEAAQd1ZHBwaW5nCnRlYW12aWV3ZXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAS8rMadB3VkcHBpbmcKdGVhbXZpZXdlcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABLys9r0HdWRwcGluZwp0ZWFtdmlld2VyA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE1eOovQd1ZHBwaW5nCnRlYW12aWV3ZXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAATV46J9B3VkcHBpbmcKdGVhbXZpZXdlcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABLys250=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:03.693568805+02:00","Elapsed":84787947,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nJMBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"nJOBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEAAATiAAS53Lj/","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.064395836+02:00","Elapsed":100743,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C9wBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"C9yFgAABAAEAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABDnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAAQABAAAE4gAEudy4/w==","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.064540427+02:00","Elapsed":76220688,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7Q4BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"7Q6BgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAABlAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.085034405+02:00","Elapsed":62901,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"keUBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Answer":"keWFgAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAAHAAB","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.085171633+02:00","Elapsed":288544,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iYIBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"iYKBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAABlAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.115439185+02:00","Elapsed":71401,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0ooBAAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Answer":"0oqFgAABAAAAAAAADnBvcm5odWJwcmVtaXVtA2NvbQAADwAB","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:12:23.115593934+02:00","Elapsed":328542,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"60MBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"60OBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQgdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Q==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.294015347+02:00","Elapsed":5019389891,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"60MBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"60OBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Qdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.300258619+02:00","Elapsed":4017680420,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZUgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAE=","Answer":"ZUiBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAEDd3d3AmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAUAAQAAC1YAEwZuZXd3ZWICY3MDdW5tA2VkdQAGbmV3d2ViAmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAEAAQAAC1YABEBqFBs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.313114962+02:00","Elapsed":4021954419,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZUgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAE=","Answer":"ZUiBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAEDd3d3AmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAUAAQAAC1YAEwZuZXd3ZWICY3MDdW5tA2VkdQAGbmV3d2ViAmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAEAAQAAC1YABEBqFBs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.316769895+02:00","Elapsed":5041323962,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ApYBAAABAAAAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ApaBgAABAAQAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAENY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAABMAJA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATACUNY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABsEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEFzkYEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.344902502+02:00","Elapsed":5656224510,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"60MBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"60OBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQgdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Q==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.40069894+02:00","Elapsed":2115988773,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ApYBAAABAAAAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ApaBgAABAAQAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAENY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAABMAJA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATACUNY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABsEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEFzkYEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.404649547+02:00","Elapsed":2706353405,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ApYBAAABAAAAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ApaBgAABAAQAAAAADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tAAABAAENY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAABMAJA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AA1jb25maWd1cmF0aW9uBWFwcGxlA2NvbQZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATACUNY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbgVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQADWNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24FYXBwbGUDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABsEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAEZTY3MwVkc2NlOQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAAAQABAAAAEwAEFzkYEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.414747653+02:00","Elapsed":4714173774,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AxsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"AxuBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.438178091+02:00","Elapsed":571330976,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"enYBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"enaFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.438344837+02:00","Elapsed":738186829,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SZgBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"SZiBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.443086443+02:00","Elapsed":568340038,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"enYBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"enaFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.443241026+02:00","Elapsed":1763508609,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZUgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAE=","Answer":"ZUiBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAEDd3d3AmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAUAAQAACyoAEwZuZXd3ZWICY3MDdW5tA2VkdQAGbmV3d2ViAmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAEAAQAACyoABEBqFBs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.470483381+02:00","Elapsed":2185799424,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K4QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwNhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"K4SBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwNhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQN3d3cDYXBpCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgCA3d3dwNhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMDd3d3A2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4BAN3d3cDYXBpCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:49.712874158+02:00","Elapsed":254442870,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6ssBAAABAAAAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAE=","Answer":"6suBgAABAAEAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAEFbGlwc2kCY2EAAAEAAQAACKYABKCZTSU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:52.112096607+02:00","Elapsed":72125539,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5NQBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"5NSBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADgkABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:56.954230137+02:00","Elapsed":72187,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7VMBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"7VOFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADgkABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:56.954385683+02:00","Elapsed":306755,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"inkBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"inmBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQAADhAAECoDnAAADwABAAAAAAAA3q0=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:57.200646644+02:00","Elapsed":118497980,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wi4BAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"wi6FgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQAADhAAECoDnAAADwABAAAAAAAA3q0=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:57.200811847+02:00","Elapsed":118815566,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+SoBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"+SqBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:57.368982314+02:00","Elapsed":131769456,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cMMBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"cMOFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:14:57.369156823+02:00","Elapsed":132029725,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DJwBAAABAAAAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"DJyBgAABAAIAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQVkZW1vcwl3aXJlZGRvdHMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA7AA8Jd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAJd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEIs4M1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:02.142518376+02:00","Elapsed":103108878,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"agEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"agGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQN3d3cDem5jAml0AAABAAEAAA4QAATBvXAq","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:06.574398323+02:00","Elapsed":1655952912,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"agEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"agGBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQN3d3cDem5jAml0AAABAAEAAA4QAATBvXAq","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:07.22646126+02:00","Elapsed":1301216873,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IHEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IHGBgAABAAUAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNyYXcRZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAFABcGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABJdlAIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAASXZUCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAABQAEl2WAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABJdlwIU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:07.907469539+02:00","Elapsed":106716989,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fvYBAAABAAAAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"fvaBgAABAAIAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABCGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABAAABKwAEaBh7UQhjc2VydmljZQh1bmRlcm5ldANvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYelE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:11.070085505+02:00","Elapsed":112773575,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5/4BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"5/6BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.020760861+02:00","Elapsed":169945482,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0TkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"0TmBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.034921806+02:00","Elapsed":184067203,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RRcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RReBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAdAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdAAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.037002175+02:00","Elapsed":193035611,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"whYBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"whaBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.053045055+02:00","Elapsed":214329741,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DSEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"DSGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.851971319+02:00","Elapsed":294246,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gmgBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gmiBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAABdEABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.902824835+02:00","Elapsed":50841008,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LfIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LfKFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAABdEABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.903052835+02:00","Elapsed":51155330,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pGwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"pGyBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQixVQB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.912292667+02:00","Elapsed":60049603,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6PQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"6PSBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.945410666+02:00","Elapsed":93338610,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QWgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"QWiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.951293465+02:00","Elapsed":232422,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FcoBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"FcqBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.953417213+02:00","Elapsed":102067528,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m7kBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"m7mFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.953627912+02:00","Elapsed":340366,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+kMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"+kOFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.95374138+02:00","Elapsed":514123,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DDkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DDmBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAABwAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHAAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHAAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:42.959691181+02:00","Elapsed":107035695,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"298BAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"29+BgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0XuYs","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:43.038486411+02:00","Elapsed":186148159,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tGsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"tGuBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAZAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAABkABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:55.007345369+02:00","Elapsed":179929214,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"etwBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"etyBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:15:55.065478964+02:00","Elapsed":235180090,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SIoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"SIqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:01.411116378+02:00","Elapsed":455053,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LLYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LLaFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:01.563706087+02:00","Elapsed":196360,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ztsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"ztuFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:01.902269646+02:00","Elapsed":196571,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5NQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"5NSBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAApAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAACkABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.703538041+02:00","Elapsed":2380988211,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RyMBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RyOBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEI6lLmQVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDRWV/c=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.71333132+02:00","Elapsed":4388026376,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5NQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"5NSBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAFAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAAAUABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.714927085+02:00","Elapsed":4390366268,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2WkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2WmBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABJwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABJwAEQOmmXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.715068988+02:00","Elapsed":4389934498,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5NQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"5NSBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAaAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAABoABB8NSyQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.715160791+02:00","Elapsed":5438833155,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.71521881+02:00","Elapsed":3398146022,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"W2EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"W2GBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAACkAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAKQAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAKQAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.715271041+02:00","Elapsed":2391306706,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3ecBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"3eeBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.715442403+02:00","Elapsed":4304816345,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3ecBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"3eeBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQixVQB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.715525179+02:00","Elapsed":3321323075,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2WkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2WmBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABKQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.7178043+02:00","Elapsed":1428894417,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2WkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2WmBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA5AAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5AAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5AAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5AAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA5AAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.720719924+02:00","Elapsed":3436808796,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0RMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"0ROBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.723313975+02:00","Elapsed":4398405278,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RyMBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RyOBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.72798826+02:00","Elapsed":5449016905,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0RMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"0ROBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.728078776+02:00","Elapsed":2404054724,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.729165237+02:00","Elapsed":1440331961,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3ecBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"3eeBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ20PFV","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.729244728+02:00","Elapsed":1336270234,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RyMBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RyOBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.730845594+02:00","Elapsed":2406801173,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0RMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"0ROBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.738721686+02:00","Elapsed":5460063265,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GG0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GG2BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.738832251+02:00","Elapsed":4414217837,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"W2EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"W2GBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAOwAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.742846019+02:00","Elapsed":5460379583,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"W2EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"W2GBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAABQAcA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAN3d3cGYW1hem9uA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAABQAaBmUxNTMxNgJjaQpha2FtYWllZGdlA25ldAAGZTE1MzE2AmNpCmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAARoe2+k","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:05.749484397+02:00","Elapsed":4424446458,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KhgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"KhiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:15.039680563+02:00","Elapsed":235916,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"g8kBAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"g8mBgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAAFAAQ27xVS","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:15.127342995+02:00","Elapsed":87981174,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z/IBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"z/KBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIanVnZ2Nhc2gDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAATYEqhP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:15.141090257+02:00","Elapsed":98371020,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KFsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"KFuBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.56326389+02:00","Elapsed":288663281,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x0MBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"x0OFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.563422341+02:00","Elapsed":306147548,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FL4BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"FL6BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.682599356+02:00","Elapsed":113898486,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4WsBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"4WuFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.682770071+02:00","Elapsed":114138102,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3v8BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"3v+BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.773860811+02:00","Elapsed":81890749,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FRUBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"FRWFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:19:34.774016371+02:00","Elapsed":82139776,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bCoBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"bCqBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.54963462+02:00","Elapsed":231787656,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4sEBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"4sGFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.54983552+02:00","Elapsed":5392229835,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fnsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"fnuBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.645955666+02:00","Elapsed":91571585,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C4UBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"C4WFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.646134875+02:00","Elapsed":91845403,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iMwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"iMyBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.736382125+02:00","Elapsed":83850974,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Pm8BAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"Pm+FgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:43.736551537+02:00","Elapsed":84096186,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9w8BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"9w+BgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADgwABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:48.243266819+02:00","Elapsed":94579,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4sEBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"4sGFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADgwABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:21:48.243408011+02:00","Elapsed":5073038507,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TMoBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TMqBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:22:45.748846248+02:00","Elapsed":183347066,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"e1oBAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"e1qBgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAO8ABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:22:45.762837977+02:00","Elapsed":197327874,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fS0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"fS2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:22:45.770357556+02:00","Elapsed":204836828,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LP0BAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"LP2BgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAAUAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAUABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:23:50.291154532+02:00","Elapsed":336493194,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LTgBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"LTiBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAAcAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAAUAECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:23:50.390767779+02:00","Elapsed":92194482,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LTgBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"LTiBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAAB0AECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:23:50.418906981+02:00","Elapsed":460939313,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lmIBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"lmKBgAABAAEAAAAABXdob2lzBHJpcGUDbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEcmlwZQNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBnwC6AAiAAAAAMEABoc=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:23:50.875198988+02:00","Elapsed":195008518,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OscBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:23:59.03291556+02:00","Elapsed":5601713670,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OscBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:04.814973519+02:00","Elapsed":6380861480,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YokBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:08.081352303+02:00","Elapsed":6384443849,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YokBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"YomBggABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:11.250350831+02:00","Elapsed":4548070874,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"p7wBAAABAAAAAAAAAjE0Ajc1AzI0OQI2Ngdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQ==","Answer":"p7yBgAABAAEAAAAAAjE0Ajc1AzI0OQI2Ngdpbi1hZGRyBGFycGEAAAwAAQIxNAI3NQMyNDkCNjYHaW4tYWRkcgRhcnBhAAAMAAEAAA4QACISY3Jhd2wtNjYtMjQ5LTc1LTE0CWdvb2dsZWJvdANjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:15.843428715+02:00","Elapsed":65899842,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WwIBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"WwKBggABAAAAAAAAAzEwOQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:17.4964528+02:00","Elapsed":45080619,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C+cBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwMQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:25.100704836+02:00","Elapsed":5941291027,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C+cBAAABAAAAAAAAAzEwMQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"C+eBggABAAAAAAAAAzEwMQMyMTEDMTI3Ajg2B2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:24:26.441577193+02:00","Elapsed":2279838549,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jY0BAAABAAAAAAAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jY2BgAABAAQAAAAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQF3CHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgBAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIBdwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4AwF3CHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgE","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:30.891641763+02:00","Elapsed":233835388,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vaMBAAABAAAAAAAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQ==","Answer":"vaOBgAABAAEAAAAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQF3CHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEAAA4QABAqA5wAAA8ADwABBe7ercDe","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:30.983277605+02:00","Elapsed":87613557,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XMABAAABAAAAAAAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"XMCBgAABAAAAAQAAAXcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAABgABAAAAswBAAWEIcmVzb2x2ZXIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ABmRvbWFpbgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwB4OUytAAAcIAAADhAAEnUAAAAAtA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:31.070739782+02:00","Elapsed":83749634,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AFQBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"AFSBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADSoABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.151189486+02:00","Elapsed":64218,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"r2oBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"r2qFgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADSoABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.151326408+02:00","Elapsed":277547,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SZABAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"SZCBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.299631963+02:00","Elapsed":125295159,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EhwBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"EhyFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.299819622+02:00","Elapsed":125527471,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CvMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"CvOBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.429859002+02:00","Elapsed":126615223,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"b8sBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"b8uFgAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:25:34.430022094+02:00","Elapsed":126871627,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PQ0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"PQ2BgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:26:49.968393081+02:00","Elapsed":236238025,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gbgBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"gbiBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADhAAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:26:50.031353208+02:00","Elapsed":59446363,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZH8BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"ZH+BgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAhYAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:26:50.09099848+02:00","Elapsed":51601790,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+GYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"+GaBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4/w==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.349986256+02:00","Elapsed":335082262,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kEgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"kEiFgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.350179325+02:00","Elapsed":506252184,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KRABAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"KRCBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.479480899+02:00","Elapsed":122327875,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oBcBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"oBeFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.47968157+02:00","Elapsed":122621250,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jewBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"jeyBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.569478004+02:00","Elapsed":85978246,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"bz4BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"bz6FgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:33:30.569653558+02:00","Elapsed":86257925,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tmcBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"tmeBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:13.840544847+02:00","Elapsed":252019734,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hBEBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"hBGBgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQAADhAAECoDnAAADwAPAAEF7t6twN4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:13.947750962+02:00","Elapsed":41673435,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hAYBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"hAaBgAABAAIAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQAADhAAFgAKBmZpbHRlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQAADhAAFgABBmZpbHRlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:14.049425758+02:00","Elapsed":91762220,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"i/IBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"i/KBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:42.780406535+02:00","Elapsed":227844814,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"aQcBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"aQeBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADhAAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:42.828934102+02:00","Elapsed":44743502,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"k60BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"k62BgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABXUAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:34:42.873221233+02:00","Elapsed":40587766,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"q0YBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"q0aBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADfYABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:08.850624341+02:00","Elapsed":191878,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"M2wBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"M2yBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADfYAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:08.853599798+02:00","Elapsed":227228,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XLkBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"XLmBgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABVwAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:08.861838754+02:00","Elapsed":173926,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YKUBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"YKWBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:22.706295985+02:00","Elapsed":331366144,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YKUBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"YKWBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:22.786521484+02:00","Elapsed":5413162276,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"a88BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"a8+BgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADhAAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:22.853680656+02:00","Elapsed":76781887,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"B24BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"B26BgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABc0AOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:22.923367821+02:00","Elapsed":62113196,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Cx8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Cx+BgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAACMAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAIwAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAIwAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:26.422190156+02:00","Elapsed":93490195,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fpcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"fpeBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAjAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAACMABB8NSyQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:26.428019683+02:00","Elapsed":96729178,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CWUBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"CWWBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEI6lLmQVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABDRWV/c=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:26.579930889+02:00","Elapsed":248659507,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MPMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"MPOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:26.580053677+02:00","Elapsed":248840594,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+IEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+IGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.345886038+02:00","Elapsed":619100,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0dwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"0dyFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.346025515+02:00","Elapsed":644760,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nP8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"nP+BgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABGQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGQAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGQAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGQAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.435128822+02:00","Elapsed":98111992,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oUsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"oUuFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.441536276+02:00","Elapsed":187305,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XV0BAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"XV2BgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.461001808+02:00","Elapsed":117701883,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DPABAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DPCBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.469890684+02:00","Elapsed":124284829,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y4oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Y4qBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.470002005+02:00","Elapsed":124741302,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eq4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"eq6BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.580476666+02:00","Elapsed":235186595,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Wl0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Wl2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:27.612946827+02:00","Elapsed":267028519,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BVcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BVeFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:30.548972187+02:00","Elapsed":240369,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"faYBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"faaBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADfkABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:45.909902131+02:00","Elapsed":11312254,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RoUBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"RoWBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADfkAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:45.931460705+02:00","Elapsed":9882206,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iL0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"iL2BgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABbYAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:35:45.952715548+02:00","Elapsed":17569968,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RuIBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"RuKBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:17.624506539+02:00","Elapsed":233009401,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y2MBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"Y2OBgAABAAEAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AABwAAQAADhAAECoDnAAADwAPAAEF7t6twN4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:17.749691969+02:00","Elapsed":119078570,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1cUBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"1cWBgAABAAIAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQAADhAAFgABBmZpbHRlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAA8AAQAADhAAFgAKBmZpbHRlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:17.859916581+02:00","Elapsed":99145475,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GtYBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GtaBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADc8ABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:28.555377833+02:00","Elapsed":15576708,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CGwBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"CGyBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADc8AECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:28.569059958+02:00","Elapsed":10636995,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0FkBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"0FmBgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABYwAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:36:28.59127948+02:00","Elapsed":14967058,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TUwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"TUyBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAABDAAEQOmnXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:00.652878727+02:00","Elapsed":192384573,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t1wBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"t1yBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmnZgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp4sHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adxB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmnZQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp4oHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adk","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:00.864420684+02:00","Elapsed":146576303,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"W/ABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"W/CBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA/wAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:01.223456521+02:00","Elapsed":142276801,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"orABAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"orCBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAABHwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHwAErcJMZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:01.742930135+02:00","Elapsed":131268803,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"N20BAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"N22BgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAEgAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEgABEDppp0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEgABEDpppwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEgABEDpppoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEgABEDppps=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:02.230705789+02:00","Elapsed":78381691,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vFEBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"vFGBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAAvABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAvAAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAvAAStwkycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAvAAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAvAAStwkya","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:02.607837226+02:00","Elapsed":93672097,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4IIBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"4IKFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:02.836648027+02:00","Elapsed":247676,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jG4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"jG6FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:15.635504134+02:00","Elapsed":271194,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5dYBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"5daBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:15.801971045+02:00","Elapsed":177999512,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NowBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"NoyBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:15.837185522+02:00","Elapsed":172597085,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X6ABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"X6CBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAABcAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAFwAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAFwAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:15.837255348+02:00","Elapsed":172670820,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OJQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"OJSBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQixVQB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:15.837401876+02:00","Elapsed":172873106,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iakBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"iamBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA4AB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAADgABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:16.693354597+02:00","Elapsed":41677503,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hhwBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"hhyBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:37:16.704226456+02:00","Elapsed":50702406,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kxMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"kxOBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:38:33.714181087+02:00","Elapsed":5341811217,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kxMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"kxOBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:38:33.715482943+02:00","Elapsed":337617674,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UJABAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"UJCBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADhAAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:38:33.805730592+02:00","Elapsed":61665470,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cKIBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"cKKBgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABmgAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:38:33.940293826+02:00","Elapsed":119714904,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7E4BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"7E6BgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADfUABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:00.981239583+02:00","Elapsed":56706014,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9YcBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"9YeBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADfUAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:01.00771144+02:00","Elapsed":132923,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GMwBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"GMyBgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABk0AOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:01.024468779+02:00","Elapsed":209426,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kwsBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"kwuBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADfAABF242CI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:06.538198807+02:00","Elapsed":172819,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fWABAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"fWCBgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AABwAAQAADfAAECYGKAACIAABAkgYkyXIGUY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:06.546412367+02:00","Elapsed":177034,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kRoBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"kRqBgAABAAAAAQAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAYAAQAABkgAOgNzbnMDZG5zBWljYW5uA29yZwADbm9jA2RucwVpY2FubgNvcmcAeEnF5AAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAADhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:06.579701234+02:00","Elapsed":212760,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8rcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"8reFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:10.368256474+02:00","Elapsed":307169,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"q30BAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"q32BgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:10.567790935+02:00","Elapsed":199801754,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"M4EBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"M4GBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA3AB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAADcABB8NSyQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:10.574753058+02:00","Elapsed":211939877,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5EcBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"5EeBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:10.582871518+02:00","Elapsed":216239520,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1h4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1h6FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.381223447+02:00","Elapsed":375316,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OsUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OsWFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.381390468+02:00","Elapsed":555677,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"anoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"anqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.51224336+02:00","Elapsed":91874,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BhUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"BhWBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.537975357+02:00","Elapsed":157136688,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QkMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"QkOBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.538134277+02:00","Elapsed":157938393,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BZQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"BZSBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAABQAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAABQAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:39:11.561814341+02:00","Elapsed":181038552,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Tj0BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"Tj2BgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.442928326+02:00","Elapsed":205833477,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MPQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"MPSFgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.443162601+02:00","Elapsed":5328623128,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5goBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"5gqBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.522887919+02:00","Elapsed":286370107,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MPQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"MPSFgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.523084983+02:00","Elapsed":409694726,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FOYBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"FOaBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.574455926+02:00","Elapsed":124241505,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dS0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"dS2FgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.574611751+02:00","Elapsed":124502457,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"A+0BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"A+2BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.668328207+02:00","Elapsed":87090331,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/vABAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"/vCFgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:27.668509585+02:00","Elapsed":87367726,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HMABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"HMCBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:46.103740849+02:00","Elapsed":219859429,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DXUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"DXWBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:46.108811889+02:00","Elapsed":224312578,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yaIBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"yaKBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:46.115853983+02:00","Elapsed":239190364,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nIsBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"nIuBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAOwAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:46.130533712+02:00","Elapsed":238972004,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dW8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"dW+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:46.900229602+02:00","Elapsed":328458,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"75gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"75iBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAYAB0Jc3Rhci1taW5pBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAlzdGFyLW1pbmkEYzEwcghmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAEAAQAAABgABLk82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:47.002453651+02:00","Elapsed":103885352,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FQoBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"FQqBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:40:47.017926872+02:00","Elapsed":118022267,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9V0BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"9V2BgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADecABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.425796246+02:00","Elapsed":124993,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GJMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GJOFgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADecABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.42594999+02:00","Elapsed":400488,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJ4BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"BJ6BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAAIoAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.437675247+02:00","Elapsed":85597,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7qIBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"7qKFgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.437826492+02:00","Elapsed":325510,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Fz8BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"Fz+BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAAIoAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.464868559+02:00","Elapsed":68773,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MfABAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"MfCFgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:09.465016805+02:00","Elapsed":306036,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WFwBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"WFyBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAABssABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:45.596373231+02:00","Elapsed":225981217,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jIYBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"jIaBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAASsAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:45.727656515+02:00","Elapsed":127429511,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CBcBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"CBeBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASsAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASsAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:41:45.790724882+02:00","Elapsed":53901809,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j38BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"j3+BgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAABq4ABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:15.566295612+02:00","Elapsed":284792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wVABAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"wVCBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAQ4AQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:15.573277508+02:00","Elapsed":180907,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gFoBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"gFqBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAQ4AHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAQ4AIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:15.577533571+02:00","Elapsed":195060,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"toMBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"toOBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAADJ8ABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:31.041841716+02:00","Elapsed":427009404,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"toMBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"toOBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAz0ABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:31.046405845+02:00","Elapsed":5437286515,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1xkBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"1xmBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAASsAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:31.116190744+02:00","Elapsed":69402802,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3FIBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"3FKBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASsAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASsAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:31.185875773+02:00","Elapsed":66204342,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mTABAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"mTCBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAzwABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:32.845051767+02:00","Elapsed":68731071,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"M1MBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"M1OBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAASoAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:32.994866103+02:00","Elapsed":113109526,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C+IBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"C+KBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASoAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAASoAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:42:33.165110521+02:00","Elapsed":89733052,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgoBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgqBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAwYABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:26.870623929+02:00","Elapsed":15533781,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L+cBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"L+eBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAPQAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:26.886575785+02:00","Elapsed":9457321,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MfkBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"MfmBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAPQAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAPQAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:26.904826641+02:00","Elapsed":12010839,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"G0QBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"G0SBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.72778425+02:00","Elapsed":308394500,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UOQBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"UOSFgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.727953751+02:00","Elapsed":344378841,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KKYBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"KKaBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.827518844+02:00","Elapsed":86588857,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"61QBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"61SFgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.82766864+02:00","Elapsed":86837772,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cSsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"cSuBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.972232004+02:00","Elapsed":137077998,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HRwBAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"HRyFgAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:45.972390941+02:00","Elapsed":137322342,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7bUBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"7bWBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADgcABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:55.65505356+02:00","Elapsed":61271,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9b8BAAABAAAAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"9b+FgAABAAEAAAAAB2V4YW1wbGUDY29tAAABAAEHZXhhbXBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADgcABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:55.655194149+02:00","Elapsed":273466,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XTwBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"XTyBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:43:55.878363339+02:00","Elapsed":143605531,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vmcBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vmeBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAroABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:42.530715089+02:00","Elapsed":13065360,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"r+IBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"r+KBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAKgAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:42.551604179+02:00","Elapsed":13270043,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FI4BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"FI6BgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAKgAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAKgAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:42.58231595+02:00","Elapsed":26372557,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SkIBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SkKBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAArkABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:43.631793797+02:00","Elapsed":37266247,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7sIBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"7sKBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAKcAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:43.670070987+02:00","Elapsed":15875538,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Pv0BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"Pv2BgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAKcAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAKcAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:43.716354887+02:00","Elapsed":36444342,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dpIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwRyZWFsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"dpKBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwRyZWFsA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwRyZWFsA2NvbQAABQABAAAKOwAKBHJlYWwDY29tAARyZWFsA2NvbQAAAQABAAAKOwAEz7wCNA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:53.859639544+02:00","Elapsed":195753396,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mJ0BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"mJ2BgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAJ0AQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:53.975157974+02:00","Elapsed":67923906,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CYABAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"CYCBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAJ0AHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAJ0AIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:54.090262054+02:00","Elapsed":73812845,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TocBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ToeBgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAq0ABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:55.821036924+02:00","Elapsed":26590932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KWABAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"KWCBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAJsAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:55.899783896+02:00","Elapsed":14874771,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jcMBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"jcOBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAJsAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAJsAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:44:56.015763117+02:00","Elapsed":30259653,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Tg0BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Tg2BgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAAAoYABM+8AjQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:34.675920203+02:00","Elapsed":13480858,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6aIBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"6aKBgAABAAAAAQAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAHQAQwlucy1tYXN0ZXIHcHJvZ25ldANjb20ADXJuLWhvc3RtYXN0ZXIEcmVhbANjb20AeEnJxQAABwgAAAOEABJ1AAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:34.68075016+02:00","Elapsed":192674,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X4EBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"X4GBgAABAAIAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAHQAHwAKCGNsdXN0ZXIxAnVzC21lc3NhZ2VsYWJzA2NvbQAEcmVhbANjb20AAA8AAQAAAHQAIAAUCWNsdXN0ZXIxYQJ1cwttZXNzYWdlbGFicwNjb20A","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:34.684922439+02:00","Elapsed":161958,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Zu0BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"Zu2BgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.474976817+02:00","Elapsed":246325833,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HZ4BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"HZ6FgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.47517502+02:00","Elapsed":376920337,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fdEBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"fdGBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAECYmwId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.575942615+02:00","Elapsed":333087855,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HZ4BAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"HZ6FgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.576131175+02:00","Elapsed":5481304558,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ks0BAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAE=","Answer":"ks2BgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAcAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.585502154+02:00","Elapsed":102996670,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0awBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"0ayFgAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.585691681+02:00","Elapsed":103275703,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Z4MBAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAE=","Answer":"Z4OBgAABAAAAAQAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAPAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAYAAQAAALMAQAFhCHJlc29sdmVyCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAZkb21haW4Id2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AeDlMrQAAHCAAAA4QABJ1AAAAALQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.701265018+02:00","Elapsed":81424992,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"N0QBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"N0SFgAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:45:45.70143711+02:00","Elapsed":81671140,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fp4BAAABAAAAAAAABmRpc25leQJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"fp6BgAABAAEAAAAABmRpc25leQJybwAAAQABBmRpc25leQJybwAAAQABAAAAEgAEaEpngA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:46:27.111731166+02:00","Elapsed":237544314,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vgsBAAABAAAAAAAABmRpc25leQJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"vguBgAABAAAAAQAABmRpc25leQJybwAAHAABBmRpc25leQJybwAABgABAAABKwBCA25zMRNkaXNuZXlpbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsA25ldAAHZG5zLW9wcwNkaWcDY29tAHhJyPwAAA4QAAACWAAJOoAAAAcI","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:46:27.239045052+02:00","Elapsed":113798892,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ukkBAAABAAAAAAAABmRpc25leQJybwAADwAB","Answer":"ukmBgAABAAMAAAAABmRpc25leQJybwAADwABBmRpc25leQJybwAADwABAAABKwAUAAoDbXhhCWV4cHVyZ2F0ZQJkZQAGZGlzbmV5AnJvAAAPAAEAAAErABUACgNteGEJZXhwdXJnYXRlA25ldAAGZGlzbmV5AnJvAAAPAAEAAAErABUACgNteGIJZXhwdXJnYXRlA25ldAA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:46:27.334448665+02:00","Elapsed":90255771,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HWABAAABAAAAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"HWCBgAABAAEAAAAAAmJsCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAADbIABLncuP4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:47:19.947712187+02:00","Elapsed":113329,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"b2oBAAABAAAAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"b2qFgAABAAEAAAAABHJlYWwDY29tAAABAAEEcmVhbANjb20AAAEAAQAADbIABLncuP4=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":4,"Rule":"phishing-shavar"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:47:19.947818559+02:00","Elapsed":293310,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1VoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"1VqBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Qdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:49.524548299+02:00","Elapsed":5667174505,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1VoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"1VqBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQgdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Q==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:49.524669228+02:00","Elapsed":4663892522,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1VoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"1VqBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Qdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:49.524759552+02:00","Elapsed":2661910734,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OL8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"OL+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.05735465+02:00","Elapsed":91488498,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BaMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"BaOBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMQAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.06653742+02:00","Elapsed":96696535,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WJMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WJOBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.082952349+02:00","Elapsed":114758192,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fJcBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"fJeBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEaMbsAQhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABCO82CM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.184499285+02:00","Elapsed":205068593,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UTwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"UTyFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.987319911+02:00","Elapsed":301792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6QEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"6QGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:51.987588546+02:00","Elapsed":573224,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DM0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"DM2BgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADIAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMgAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAMgAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106343707+02:00","Elapsed":121477986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Yp8BAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Yp+BgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEPZm9yY2VzYWZlc2VhcmNoBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106437204+02:00","Elapsed":119362404,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"XLQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"XLSFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106515934+02:00","Elapsed":183341,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"utUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"utWFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106568102+02:00","Elapsed":119545880,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qgwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"qgyFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106603122+02:00","Elapsed":266657,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0vABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"0vCBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.106667652+02:00","Elapsed":119678193,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4X0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"4X2BgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0zxnR","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:52.129116864+02:00","Elapsed":139321621,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v6sBAAABAAAAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"v6uBgAABAAEAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQl3aXJlZGRvdHMObWV0YWxvZ2ljc3NvZnQDY29tAAABAAEAAASvAAREQXpn","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:54.067847554+02:00","Elapsed":170224870,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cncBAAABAAAAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"cneBgAABAAUAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNyYXcRZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABcGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2WAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwIU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:54.928310588+02:00","Elapsed":123170792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kDoBAAABAAAAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"kDqBgAABAAIAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABCGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABAAABKwAEaBh7UQhjc2VydmljZQh1bmRlcm5ldANvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYelE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:48:58.611363498+02:00","Elapsed":102101353,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nX0BAAABAAAAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"nX2BgAABAAIAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQVkZW1vcwl3aXJlZGRvdHMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA7AA8Jd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAJd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEIs4M1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:03.313055116+02:00","Elapsed":79019060,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0iQBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"0iSBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:05.610175645+02:00","Elapsed":102936361,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7/8BAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"7/+BgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAADCAABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:05.799823958+02:00","Elapsed":291553328,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"01IBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"01KBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAABQABAAAHagANB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAdwb3JuaHViA2NvbQAAAQABAAAHagAE2BKoEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:19.099766227+02:00","Elapsed":176760848,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KBwBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"KByBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:19.236469583+02:00","Elapsed":110380356,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rrYBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"rraFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:19.236603004+02:00","Elapsed":132177892,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"obYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"obaBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACzAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:19.326682776+02:00","Elapsed":86848745,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"950BAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"952FgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:19.326836966+02:00","Elapsed":87083522,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3ZMBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"3ZOBgAABAAEAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4/w==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.958135668+02:00","Elapsed":86296521,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8tsBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"8tuFgAABAAEAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAABAAEHcG9ybmh1YgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuP8=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.958287103+02:00","Elapsed":86537473,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"U68BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAAB","Answer":"U6+BgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAHAABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACwAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.964424483+02:00","Elapsed":73935,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OhgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Answer":"OhiFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAcAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.964563764+02:00","Elapsed":292340,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KfABAAABAAAAAAAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwAB","Answer":"KfCBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JsZgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAADwABCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAAGAAEAAACwAEABYQhyZXNvbHZlcgh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAGZG9tYWluCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAHg5TK0AABwgAAAOEAASdQAAAAC0","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.975177159+02:00","Elapsed":59287,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EZgBAAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Answer":"EZiFgAABAAAAAAAAB3Bvcm5odWIDY29tAAAPAAE=","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":5,"Rule":"parental CATEGORY_BLACKLISTED"},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:49:22.97529029+02:00","Elapsed":244630,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BVsBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BVuBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAABAAEAAAErAARoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQAAASsABGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:31.865205642+02:00","Elapsed":13509617044,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BVsBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BVuBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAABAAEAAAEpAARoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQAAASkABGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:34.229108198+02:00","Elapsed":10878866247,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CtkBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"CtmBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAABAAEAAAEmAARoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQAAASYABGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:36.939457579+02:00","Elapsed":5851577019,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CtkBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"CtmBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAABAAEAAAEkAARoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQAAASQABGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:39.692100698+02:00","Elapsed":3613817637,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vm4BAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQ==","Answer":"vm6BgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAcAAEAAAErABAmBkcAADAAAAAAAABoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQAAASsAECYGRwAAMAAAAAAAAGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:42.615272007+02:00","Elapsed":5631939682,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vm4BAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQ==","Answer":"vm6BgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAcAAEAAAEpABAmBkcAADAAAAAAAABoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQAAASkAECYGRwAAMAAAAAAAAGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:45.043811365+02:00","Elapsed":3072366223,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jdwBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"jdyBgAABAAAAAQAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAGAAEAAAcHAEEFYWxpY2UCbnMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AA2RucwpjbG91ZGZsYXJlA2NvbQB44oSxAAAnEAAACWAACTqAAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:47.827490073+02:00","Elapsed":5204221933,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jdwBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"jdyBgAABAAAAAQAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAGAAEAAAcFAEEFYWxpY2UCbnMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AA2RucwpjbG91ZGZsYXJlA2NvbQB44oSxAAAnEAAACWAACTqAAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:57:50.391326564+02:00","Elapsed":2757946248,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1H8BAAABAAAAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"1H+BgAABAAQAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4BANhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEDYXBpCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgCA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4Aw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:58:04.844053336+02:00","Elapsed":234937119,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J+YBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"J+aBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAABAAEAAADDAARoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAAEAAQAAAMMABGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:16.408076786+02:00","Elapsed":2829756622,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ploBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQ==","Answer":"plqBgAABAAIAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAcAAEAAADOABAmBkcAADAAAAAAAABoG5BmCXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAABwAAQAAAM4AECYGRwAAMAAAAAAAAGgbkWY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:16.511734477+02:00","Elapsed":234126,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"aAcBAAABAAAAAAAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQ==","Answer":"aAeBgAABAAAAAQAACXBvcm5vc2V4ZQNiaXoAAA8AAQlwb3Jub3NleGUDYml6AAAGAAEAAAavAEEFYWxpY2UCbnMKY2xvdWRmbGFyZQNjb20AA2RucwpjbG91ZGZsYXJlA2NvbQB44oSxAAAnEAAACWAACTqAAAAOEA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:16.524539064+02:00","Elapsed":198935,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Dj4BAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Dj6BgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAErAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:30.187464056+02:00","Elapsed":5868025541,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EnkBAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AABwAAQ==","Answer":"EnmBgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AABwAAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAErAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:30.247398745+02:00","Elapsed":54726600,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Fe4BAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"Fe6BgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAA8AAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAErAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:30.311035901+02:00","Elapsed":47950574,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+4sBAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"+4uBgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAEqAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:31.997541463+02:00","Elapsed":195432,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OjMBAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AABwAAQ==","Answer":"OjOBgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AABwAAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAEqAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:32.00536071+02:00","Elapsed":175170,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9jIBAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"9jKBgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAA8AAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAEqAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:32.075903239+02:00","Elapsed":202262,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Dj4BAAABAAAAAAAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Dj6BgAABAAAAAQAADHNvbWVwb3Juc2l0ZQNjb20AAAEAAQxzb21lcG9ybnNpdGUDY29tAAAGAAEAAAEpAFQLbnMtY2xvdWQtZTENZ29vZ2xlZG9tYWlucwNjb20AFGNsb3VkLWRucy1ob3N0bWFzdGVyBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAAAAQAAVGAAAA4QAAP0gAAAASw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T21:59:32.783937025+02:00","Elapsed":3472203076,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C9EBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQAB","Answer":"C9GBgAABAAQAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZd1ANibmMCbHQAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXeMDYm5jAmx0AAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2/A2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdNg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:01:57.71608199+02:00","Elapsed":11171593374,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"C9EBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQAB","Answer":"C9GBgAABAAQAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAOQAENuZd1ANibmMCbHQAAAEAAQAAADkABDbmXeMDYm5jAmx0AAABAAEAAAA5AAQ25l2/A2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAOQAENuZdNg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:00.179502756+02:00","Elapsed":8563687369,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4TcBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQAB","Answer":"4TeBgAABAAQAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAMgAENuZd1ANibmMCbHQAAAEAAQAAADIABDbmXeMDYm5jAmx0AAABAAEAAAAyAAQ25l2/A2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAAMgAENuZdNg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:07.715945655+02:00","Elapsed":174899,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VeIBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAHAAB","Answer":"VeKBgAABAAgAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOwAQJgCQACAMjAAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADsAECYAkAAgDAIAAAFxReiAk6EDYm5jAmx0AAAcAAEAAAA7ABAmAJAAIAz6AAABcUXogJOhA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOwAQJgCQACAMTAAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADsAECYAkAAgDNQAAAFxReiAk6EDYm5jAmx0AAAcAAEAAAA7ABAmAJAAIAzoAAABcUXogJOhA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOwAQJgCQACAMfgAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADsAECYAkAAgDMQAAAFxReiAk6E=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:07.916843279+02:00","Elapsed":196984284,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DzoBAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAADwAB","Answer":"DzqBgAABAAAAAQAAA2JuYwJsdAAADwABA2JuYwJsdAAABgABAAADgwBLB25zLTE5MjUJYXdzZG5zLTQ4AmNvAnVrABFhd3NkbnMtaG9zdG1hc3RlcgZhbWF6b24DY29tAAAAAAEAABwgAAADhAASdQAAAVGA","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:08.300438203+02:00","Elapsed":52205730,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8F0BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQAB","Answer":"8F2BgAABAAQAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABA2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAALQAENuZd1ANibmMCbHQAAAEAAQAAAC0ABDbmXeMDYm5jAmx0AAABAAEAAAAtAAQ25l2/A2JuYwJsdAAAAQABAAAALQAENuZdNg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:11.785135244+02:00","Elapsed":195892,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Yv0BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAHAAB","Answer":"Yv2BgAABAAgAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOAAQJgCQACAMjAAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADgAECYAkAAgDAIAAAFxReiAk6EDYm5jAmx0AAAcAAEAAAA4ABAmAJAAIAz6AAABcUXogJOhA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOAAQJgCQACAMTAAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADgAECYAkAAgDNQAAAFxReiAk6EDYm5jAmx0AAAcAAEAAAA4ABAmAJAAIAzoAAABcUXogJOhA2JuYwJsdAAAHAABAAAAOAAQJgCQACAMfgAAAXFF6ICToQNibmMCbHQAABwAAQAAADgAECYAkAAgDMQAAAFxReiAk6E=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:11.789429945+02:00","Elapsed":182461,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gp0BAAABAAAAAAAAA2JuYwJsdAAADwAB","Answer":"gp2BgAABAAAAAQAAA2JuYwJsdAAADwABA2JuYwJsdAAABgABAAADgABLB25zLTE5MjUJYXdzZG5zLTQ4AmNvAnVrABFhd3NkbnMtaG9zdG1hc3RlcgZhbWF6b24DY29tAAAAAAEAABwgAAADhAASdQAAAVGA","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:02:11.798498068+02:00","Elapsed":182356,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"QNYBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"QNaBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACqwABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:20.366695689+02:00","Elapsed":135348,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KWABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"KWCFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQN3d3cGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAABAAEAAAqsAATY7yZ4","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:20.366818661+02:00","Elapsed":324674,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZfEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ZfGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:38.15886882+02:00","Elapsed":245583,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FDEBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"FDGBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:38.299678568+02:00","Elapsed":169058661,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2S8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"2S+BgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADIAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMgAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAMgAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:38.33061286+02:00","Elapsed":177855970,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KYMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KYOBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAFAAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:38.479062961+02:00","Elapsed":19551384732,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KYMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KYOBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAEgAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:41.191814283+02:00","Elapsed":19259498983,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5x0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"5x2BgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIsHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxkB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMcQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIoHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:55.167165698+02:00","Elapsed":35926157773,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yS8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"yS+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAbAAEQOm4Xg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:03:55.168785723+02:00","Elapsed":35313900591,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"5x0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"5x2BgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAErcJMZgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABK3CTIsHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEjAAStwkxkB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABIwAErcJMcQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABK3CTIoHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEjAAStwkxl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:03.238874376+02:00","Elapsed":42973129649,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KYMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"KYOBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA+AAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:03.282780036+02:00","Elapsed":43343659862,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yS8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"yS+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAXwAEQOm4Xg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:08.77045227+02:00","Elapsed":47939674988,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:11.558561469+02:00","Elapsed":49437567242,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASgABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASgABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASgABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASgABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:15.006324913+02:00","Elapsed":51881840792,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASYABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASYABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASYABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASYABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:17.066365769+02:00","Elapsed":51934732080,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASMABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:19.80703251+02:00","Elapsed":50677775451,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASEABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASEABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASEABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASEABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:22.554895118+02:00","Elapsed":29415781457,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wPYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wPaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAARsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAARsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAARsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAARsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:04:28.023705801+02:00","Elapsed":50892230922,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAErACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:24.034948525+02:00","Elapsed":72056861394,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D0UBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"D0WBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAEpACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAASkABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAEpAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAABKQAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAASkABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAEpAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABKQAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAASkABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAEpAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABKQAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAASkABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAEpAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABKQAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:26.070345434+02:00","Elapsed":177115,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAODwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADg8ABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4PAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAODwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:29.513472896+02:00","Elapsed":77585292304,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB2ABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB2AARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB2AAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB2AARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB2AARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB2AARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:29.61461678+02:00","Elapsed":77688129639,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oOABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"oOCBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAByABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAByAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAByAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAByAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAByAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAByAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:34.046928605+02:00","Elapsed":194158,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"f7cBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"f7eBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOCwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADgsABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4LAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOCwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:34.05494578+02:00","Elapsed":227129,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mCkBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"mCmFgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:34.699018923+02:00","Elapsed":306388,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1pgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"1piFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:34.699167521+02:00","Elapsed":496932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOCgAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADgoABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4KAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOCgAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:35.094317554+02:00","Elapsed":82149805986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAACJAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:35.13088582+02:00","Elapsed":83152813956,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Cg8BAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Cg+FgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:36.879742449+02:00","Elapsed":199435,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABrABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABrAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABrAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABrAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABrAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABrAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:40.709487602+02:00","Elapsed":57763320898,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOBAAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADgQABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA4EAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAOBAAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:40.710332217+02:00","Elapsed":57760546663,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAB+AATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:46.330758767+02:00","Elapsed":63346992429,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAEVACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAARUABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAEVAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAABFQAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAARUABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAEVAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABFQAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAARUABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAEVAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABFQAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAARUABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAEVAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABFQAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:46.33090355+02:00","Elapsed":63345966489,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAB7AATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:50.076619067+02:00","Elapsed":243455,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABgABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABgAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABgAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABgAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABgAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABgAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:51.975038209+02:00","Elapsed":99046841231,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAB5AATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:51.975704077+02:00","Elapsed":98995279588,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABdABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABdAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABdAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABdAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABdAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABdAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:54.761322309+02:00","Elapsed":99825521847,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAEKACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAQoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAEKAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAABCgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAQoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAEKAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABCgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAQoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAEKAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABCgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAQoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAEKAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABCgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:05:57.527050611+02:00","Elapsed":104529614972,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABXABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABXAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABXAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABXAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABXAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABXAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:01.037801471+02:00","Elapsed":102092994944,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAABtAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:03.149799685+02:00","Elapsed":108171625185,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAECACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAQIABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAECAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAABAgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAQIABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAECAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABAgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAQIABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAECAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABAgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAQIABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAECAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAABAgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:05.898794702+02:00","Elapsed":110919977135,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN6AAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADegABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA3oAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN6AAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:08.725423179+02:00","Elapsed":109780694398,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RNsBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"RNuBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN5QAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADeUABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA3lAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN5QAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:11.533608295+02:00","Elapsed":69710186350,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P/0BAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"P/2BgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAD2ACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAPYABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAD2AARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAA9gAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAPYABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAD2AARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAA9gAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAPYABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAD2AARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAA9gAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAPYABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAD2AARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAA9gAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:17.255883315+02:00","Elapsed":75424475633,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"F5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAABfAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:17.260330812+02:00","Elapsed":75434211561,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GgQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GgSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABBABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABBAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABBAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABBAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABBAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABBAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:22.913391038+02:00","Elapsed":81081925095,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RNsBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"RNuBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN2gAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADdoABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA3aAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAAN2gAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:22.917212037+02:00","Elapsed":80088471833,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GgQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"GgSBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA9ABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAA9AARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAA9AAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAA9AARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAA9AARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAA9AARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:26.840130303+02:00","Elapsed":84010086828,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"F5UBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"F5WBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAABRAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:31.162087202+02:00","Elapsed":88332069566,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"P/0BAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"P/2BgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAADoACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAOgABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAADoAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAA6AAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAOgABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAADoAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAA6AAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAOgABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAADoAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAA6AAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAOgABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAADoAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAA6AAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:31.221210068+02:00","Elapsed":88391193922,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANzAAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADcwABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA3MAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANzAAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:36.813864053+02:00","Elapsed":141877518577,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ixkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ixmBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAzAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:36.819205239+02:00","Elapsed":92251248757,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GqEBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"GqGBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANxgAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADcYABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA3GAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANxgAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:42.513850237+02:00","Elapsed":97937750814,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z/8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"z/+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAABGAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:42.513896835+02:00","Elapsed":97937731018,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LOMBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LOOBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAADXACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAANcABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAADXAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAA1wAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAANcABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAADXAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAA1wAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAANcABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAADXAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAA1wAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAANcABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAADXAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAA1wAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:48.122826057+02:00","Elapsed":103546702032,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ixkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ixmBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAoABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAoAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAoAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAoAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAoAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAoAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:48.127316971+02:00","Elapsed":102538894815,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LOMBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LOOBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAADVACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAANUABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAADVAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAA1QAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAANUABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAADVAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAA1QAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAANUABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAADVAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAA1QAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAANUABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAADVAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAA1QAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:50.875268809+02:00","Elapsed":105256624538,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z/8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"z/+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:53.617578641+02:00","Elapsed":107998950974,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GqEBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"GqGBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANuQAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADbkABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA25AASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANuQAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:56.40134129+02:00","Elapsed":110782711433,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA1AATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:06:59.197503347+02:00","Elapsed":160210405214,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GqEBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"GqGBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANsAAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADbAABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2wAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANsAAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:04.881986598+02:00","Elapsed":117306076054,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ixkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ixmBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAXABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAXAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAXAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAXAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAXAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAAXAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:04.892082298+02:00","Elapsed":117316517387,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z/8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"z/+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAtAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:07.650276686+02:00","Elapsed":120073840086,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LOMBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LOOBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAADBACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAMEABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAADBAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAwQAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAMEABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAADBAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAwQAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAMEABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAADBAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAwQAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAMEABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAADBAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAwQAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:10.426538419+02:00","Elapsed":122850516823,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAC+ACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAL4ABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAAC+AARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAvgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAL4ABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAC+AARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAvgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAL4ABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAAC+AARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAvgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAL4ABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAC+AARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAvgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:13.30942016+02:00","Elapsed":174322306913,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ixkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ixmBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAALABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAALAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAALAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAALAARA6aZfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAALAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAALAARA6adf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:16.92084519+02:00","Elapsed":125331134738,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"z/8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"z/+BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAiAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:18.869924196+02:00","Elapsed":127261935169,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GqEBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"GqGBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANnwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZ8ABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2fAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANnwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:21.851493202+02:00","Elapsed":130243502690,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LOMBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LOOBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACzACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAALMABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACzAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAswAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAALMABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACzAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAswAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAALMABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACzAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAswAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAALMABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACzAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAswAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:24.622737596+02:00","Elapsed":133002941267,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0SABAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"0SCBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANmQAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZkABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2ZAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANmQAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:28.20111249+02:00","Elapsed":181252869679,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Z1MBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Z1OBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB0ABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB0AARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB0AARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAB0AAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:32.993855846+02:00","Elapsed":138301586404,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lXQBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"lXSBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANlAAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZQABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2UAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANlAAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.278018594+02:00","Elapsed":138584852856,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wsYBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wsaBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACqACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.989372701+02:00","Elapsed":139214320613,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gxQBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gxSBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996152706+02:00","Elapsed":187047960463,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Z1MBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Z1OBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996251588+02:00","Elapsed":138279221066,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lXQBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"lXSBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZMABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2TAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996363261+02:00","Elapsed":138272757704,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wsYBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wsaBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACqACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996494698+02:00","Elapsed":138184383261,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0BIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"0BKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996549344+02:00","Elapsed":138184436709,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0BIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"0BKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996583513+02:00","Elapsed":139221509299,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"f7cBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"f7eBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZMABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2TAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996652592+02:00","Elapsed":134961037763,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vagBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vaiBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACqACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996775024+02:00","Elapsed":187015449307,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.99680582+02:00","Elapsed":134934158067,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oOABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"oOCBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996876588+02:00","Elapsed":134962184025,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.996955204+02:00","Elapsed":133939003552,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"f7cBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"f7eBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZMABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2TAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.997050765+02:00","Elapsed":133956227446,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oOABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"oOCBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.997096029+02:00","Elapsed":131950776212,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D0UBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"D0WBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACqACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.997170651+02:00","Elapsed":134934482780,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oOABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"oOCBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.997178153+02:00","Elapsed":133958007803,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D0UBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"D0WBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACqACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKoABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACqAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqgAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:33.997237465+02:00","Elapsed":133938449014,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"f7cBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"f7eBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZMABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2TAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.064570882+02:00","Elapsed":132015040964,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D0UBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"D0WBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAACpACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAAKkABGgQHiLALwABAAEAAACpAARoEAAjwC8AAQABAAAAqQAEaBACI8AvAAEAAQAAAKkABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAACpAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAAAqQAEaBABI8AvAAEAAQAAAKkABGgQHyLALwABAAEAAACpAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAAAqQAEaBADI8AvAAEAAQAAAKkABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAACpAARoEBoiwC8AAQABAAAAqQAEaBAZIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.064657211+02:00","Elapsed":131995766237,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.064693699+02:00","Elapsed":131996884635,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2L0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"2L2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.06485224+02:00","Elapsed":187084390005,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"f7cBAAABAAAAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"f7eBgAABAAQAAAAAA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2UBRQNjZG4Hc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADZMABJdlQUUDY2RuB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEAAA2TAASXZYFFA2Nkbgdzc3RhdGljA25ldAAAAQABAAANkwAEl2XBRQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.06492601+02:00","Elapsed":128000690254,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.065011517+02:00","Elapsed":127997154210,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oOABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"oOCBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABzABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAABzAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.065092188+02:00","Elapsed":128014249907,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"BJoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"BJqBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAATAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.065171095+02:00","Elapsed":119988022949,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACbABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACbAARA6aedCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACbAARA6aecCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACbAARA6aeaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACbAARA6aeb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.20457071+02:00","Elapsed":119505927891,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB9ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYya","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.345834875+02:00","Elapsed":104657643497,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACDABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACDAAStwkycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACDAAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACDAAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACDAAStwkyd","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.345972537+02:00","Elapsed":118660935912,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAC8ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkyc","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.346036725+02:00","Elapsed":88656698308,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAC8ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC8AAStwkyc","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.34607814+02:00","Elapsed":116658833100,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEdABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEdAAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEdAAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEdAAStwkybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEdAAStwkyc","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.346127524+02:00","Elapsed":112587697423,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FHwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"FHyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB9ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB9AARKfYya","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.346283463+02:00","Elapsed":56652568034,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372285179+02:00","Elapsed":118686430292,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372425833+02:00","Elapsed":119673736231,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372505186+02:00","Elapsed":116682538581,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372535295+02:00","Elapsed":88683204170,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372610398+02:00","Elapsed":104679587992,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.372672747+02:00","Elapsed":56679004581,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JcwBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JcyBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.391638022+02:00","Elapsed":112633226293,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"O1IBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"O1KFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.595246931+02:00","Elapsed":204365,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ldwBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"ldyBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAQ0AHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQ0ABK3CTJoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQ0ABK3CTJsIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQ0ABK3CTJ0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAQ0ABK3CTJw=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.649279008+02:00","Elapsed":56078441,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zJQBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"zJSBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAABgABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABgAARKfYWbCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABgAARKfYWcCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABgAARKfYWdCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABgAARKfYWa","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:34.64934138+02:00","Elapsed":56704023,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JuIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JuKBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAZwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAZwAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAZwAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAZwAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:37.849014741+02:00","Elapsed":46702437,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0VkBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"0VmBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:37.849113374+02:00","Elapsed":51667612,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cFoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"cFqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:37.855181364+02:00","Elapsed":56256009,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AzUBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"AzWBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:37.859626686+02:00","Elapsed":56814605,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rU8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"rU+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.821341899+02:00","Elapsed":227204,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Z0ABAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Z0CBgAABAAIAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEI7zYIwhtaXhwYW5lbANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGjG7AE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.883088911+02:00","Elapsed":67235812,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AJgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AJiBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdyYXBsZWFmA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAE2FeUcg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.898365604+02:00","Elapsed":77334696,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YMgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"YMiBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAJBRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tABRwcm9kdWN0aW9uLXVzLWVhc3QtMQlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ20PFV","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.898549552+02:00","Elapsed":77496252,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8jwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"8jyFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.910101923+02:00","Elapsed":198081,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rdABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rdCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOAARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA4AATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOAAEwABQ8gJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADgABMAAUPACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA4AATAAFDv","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.910296403+02:00","Elapsed":89267568,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"emwBAAABAAAAAAAAB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"emyBgAABAAEAAAAAB3NzdGF0aWMDbmV0AAABAAEHc3N0YXRpYwNuZXQAAAEAAQAADg8ABMb8zhA=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:38.932685523+02:00","Elapsed":111686554,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"H/cBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"H/eFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:39.016515853+02:00","Elapsed":261447,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VQcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"VQeFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":".doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:39.016676423+02:00","Elapsed":378041,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"eKgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"eKiBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEDd3d3BmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAFAN3d3cDY2RuBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AA3d3dwNjZG4GYW1hem9uA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwAfDmQzYWc0aHVra2g2MnluCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AA5kM2FnNGh1a2toNjJ5bgpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAOwAENFW9eQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:39.065036744+02:00","Elapsed":155131239,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZU8BAAABAAAAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ZU+BgAABAAEAAAAAC2FkdmVydGlzaW5nBmFtYXpvbgNjb20AAAEAAQthZHZlcnRpc2luZwZhbWF6b24DY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ0XuYs","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:07:39.098519292+02:00","Elapsed":82193803,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:08:41.465315741+02:00","Elapsed":179668160,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NL4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NL6BgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAASQAESn2FXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:20.783686447+02:00","Elapsed":148267240,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"0b8BAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"0b+BgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMigdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTHEHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxkB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZgdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIsHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxl","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:20.791836386+02:00","Elapsed":142800572,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jFIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"jFKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAdAAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:20.952863739+02:00","Elapsed":51013402,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CNMBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"CNOBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACUABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAACUAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAACUAAStwkxfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAACUAARCZgFf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:51.707837133+02:00","Elapsed":159982506,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Af4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Af6BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAACSAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:51.745896308+02:00","Elapsed":166631757,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v7EBAAABAAAAAAAACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"v7GFgwABAAAAAQAACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAYhlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||pagead46.l.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:52.177037302+02:00","Elapsed":195656,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UWoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"UWqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:52.184465244+02:00","Elapsed":239116,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cz4BAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"cz6FgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:52.184639886+02:00","Elapsed":381354,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"G1wBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"G1yFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:09:54.329224896+02:00","Elapsed":191115,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Rt4BAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"Rt6BgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:13:16.430090153+02:00","Elapsed":173125951,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4dwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4dyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAegATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAegAEbLEPiw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:14:04.56016932+02:00","Elapsed":283056111034,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"OyUBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"OyWBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmniwdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2QHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adlB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmnigdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2YHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adx","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:29.373045998+02:00","Elapsed":234616261,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6XYBAAABAAAAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"6XaBgAABAAQAAAAADXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABAAENc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlAUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlgUUNc3RhY2tvdmVyZmxvdwNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlwUU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:42.243908608+02:00","Elapsed":164927137,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9cABAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"9cCBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAADvAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:42.681892033+02:00","Elapsed":46641694,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LfwBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LfyBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAErACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQASPALwABAAEAAAErAARoEAMjwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAAI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQAiPALwABAAEAAAErAARoEBgiwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAcIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGiLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB4iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAZIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGyLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB8iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAdIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:42.851035584+02:00","Elapsed":183290466,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CsEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"CsGFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:42.990413278+02:00","Elapsed":272905,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VqQBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"VqSFgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:42.990706509+02:00","Elapsed":555983,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NnsBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NnuFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:16:44.687314314+02:00","Elapsed":278538,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"dZkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"dZmBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABJABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABJAARA6aebCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABJAARA6aedCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABJAARA6aeaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABJAARA6aec","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.50603949+02:00","Elapsed":278659197,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nm0BAAABAAAAAAAABWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"nm2BgAABAAMAAAAABWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQABBWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAABQABAAAANQASA2FwaQhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AA2FwaQhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAUAAQAAADUAGARzdGFyBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAARzdGFyBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAABAAEAAAA1AAS5PNgP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.523166265+02:00","Elapsed":248226830,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nVEBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoMxFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"nVGBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoMxFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDMRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAADmACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAAOYABEDpuIQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.523230213+02:00","Elapsed":308945679,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"l04BAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"l06BgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.529274531+02:00","Elapsed":254507001,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X3MBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoNBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"X3OBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoNBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDQRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAErACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEp9hYQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.607863442+02:00","Elapsed":240513968,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lkgBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"lkiBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDURZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAjACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAACMABGyxD4Q=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.607912127+02:00","Elapsed":240962625,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"U10BAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"U12FgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:15.838585685+02:00","Elapsed":219857,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"S68BAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"S6+BgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAErABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+cCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+b","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:16.001801082+02:00","Elapsed":163358301,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/jEBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"/jGBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAACMAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAACMABGyxD5oIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAACMABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAACMABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAACMABGyxD5w=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:16.002146707+02:00","Elapsed":163701326,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jXYBAAABAAAAAAAAEnBsYXRmb3JtLWxvb2thc2lkZQVmYnNieANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jXaBgAABAAIAAAAAEnBsYXRmb3JtLWxvb2thc2lkZQVmYnNieANjb20AAAEAARJwbGF0Zm9ybS1sb29rYXNpZGUFZmJzYngDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAnABcIc2NvbnRlbnQCeHgFZmJjZG4DbmV0AAhzY29udGVudAJ4eAVmYmNkbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAACcABB8NSww=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:16.064440156+02:00","Elapsed":126312914,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4/oBAAABAAAAAAAACHNjb250ZW50Anh4BWZiY2RuA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"4/qBgAABAAEAAAAACHNjb250ZW50Anh4BWZiY2RuA25ldAAAAQABCHNjb250ZW50Anh4BWZiY2RuA25ldAAAAQABAAAAJQAEuTzYEw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:16.06446674+02:00","Elapsed":126341708,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"u9oBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"u9qFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:56.570849139+02:00","Elapsed":175274,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"s7kBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"s7mBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAqwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAqwAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:56.648033126+02:00","Elapsed":198311101,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"K8MBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NzaQdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"K8OBgAABABAAAAAAA2NzaQdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABwAwAAQABAAAAqgAEQOm4XsAMAAEAAQAAAKoABEDpuHjADAABAAEAAACqAARKfX5ewAwAAQABAAAAqgAESn1+eMAMAAEAAQAAAKoABGyxDF7ADAABAAEAAACqAARssQx4wAwAAQABAAAAqgAESn0XXsAMAAEAAQAAAKoABEp9F3jADAABAAEAAACqAARKfchewAwAAQABAAAAqgAESn3IeMAMAAEAAQAAAKoABEp9HF7ADAABAAEAAACqAARKfRx4wAwAAQABAAAAqgAEQOmrXsAMAAEAAQAAAKoABEDpq3jADAABAAEAAACqAARA6aFewAwAAQABAAAAqgAEQOmheA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:17:57.209816302+02:00","Elapsed":63289537,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WUwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WUyBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEYABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAARgABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:18:02.237454937+02:00","Elapsed":58741597,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"qwQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"qwSFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:18:11.347131011+02:00","Elapsed":137216,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+LkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+LmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAACAAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAIABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAIAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:18:11.462184638+02:00","Elapsed":63485401,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+fgBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+fiFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:18:13.496298166+02:00","Elapsed":214835,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4dwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4dyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330130321+02:00","Elapsed":581832211030,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4igBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4iiBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330464543+02:00","Elapsed":577684648107,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+h4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+h6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330568984+02:00","Elapsed":576401595657,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4dwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"4dyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330671656+02:00","Elapsed":579828891107,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+h4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+h6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330743532+02:00","Elapsed":577403402901,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4igBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4iiBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330779319+02:00","Elapsed":574693827200,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4igBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4iiBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330836712+02:00","Elapsed":576697850105,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4igBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4iiBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.330942806+02:00","Elapsed":562688407754,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+h4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+h6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.331028745+02:00","Elapsed":574391707575,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4igBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4iiBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.331112568+02:00","Elapsed":570688664678,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+h4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+h6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.332149947+02:00","Elapsed":570390125097,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+h4BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+h6BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.332609338+02:00","Elapsed":562387516184,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UtUBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"UtWBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.333155809+02:00","Elapsed":537968665318,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wzMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wzOBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.333283127+02:00","Elapsed":530447336279,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UtUBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"UtWBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.333544591+02:00","Elapsed":536968414029,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ijcBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ijeBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.33363293+02:00","Elapsed":530163385064,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"UtUBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"UtWBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.333772512+02:00","Elapsed":534968441082,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wzMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"wzOBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.333905664+02:00","Elapsed":529514219083,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ijcBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ijeBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.334186888+02:00","Elapsed":529147862656,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NhkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NhmBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.337813803+02:00","Elapsed":505789562425,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NhkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NhmBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.337991553+02:00","Elapsed":502776917249,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PrEBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PrGBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.339858972+02:00","Elapsed":495801704204,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NhkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NhmBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.340695899+02:00","Elapsed":504789897289,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PrEBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PrGBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.341529834+02:00","Elapsed":494802221099,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PEgBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PEiBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.342199359+02:00","Elapsed":488562385168,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"NhkBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"NhmBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.342960857+02:00","Elapsed":498789282110,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PrEBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PrGBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.344268836+02:00","Elapsed":488798890486,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PEgBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PEiBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.344570271+02:00","Elapsed":492569489376,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PEgBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PEiBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.344857437+02:00","Elapsed":494570049587,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PEgBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PEiBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAaAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBcQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAaAAEQmYBZA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.344919243+02:00","Elapsed":495578233783,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PrEBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"PrGBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAADaABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAANoABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.344967445+02:00","Elapsed":492809229722,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAADVABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADVAARssQ+cCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADVAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADVAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADVAARssQ+b","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.53055946+02:00","Elapsed":453542909073,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2GoBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2GqBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEgAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAASABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAASAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.530758354+02:00","Elapsed":551293958000,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAC+ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC+AARA6aacCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC+AARA6aadCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC+AARA6aabCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAC+AARA6aaa","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.530817546+02:00","Elapsed":477553832603,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAADQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAANABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAANAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.530885733+02:00","Elapsed":469495537932,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2GoBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2GqBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABgAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAGABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAGAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.530989603+02:00","Elapsed":545334119378,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L5kBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"L5mBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAACgAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAKABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAKAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.531122645+02:00","Elapsed":524590811311,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2GoBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2GqBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAFABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.531229607+02:00","Elapsed":552346978502,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TD0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TD2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553148855+02:00","Elapsed":345316696084,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TD0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TD2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553348631+02:00","Elapsed":333305021779,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553459622+02:00","Elapsed":481513159004,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L5kBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"L5mBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553613923+02:00","Elapsed":527620744059,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L5kBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"L5mBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAADQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAANABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAANAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553716846+02:00","Elapsed":520611859444,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2GoBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2GqBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.553802909+02:00","Elapsed":549362298875,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TD0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TD2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.577972926+02:00","Elapsed":347346246764,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578386145+02:00","Elapsed":357506319663,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACdABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACdAARKfYyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACdAARKfYybCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACdAARKfYycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACdAARKfYyd","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578486972+02:00","Elapsed":484606089900,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEqABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEqAARA6aabCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEqAARA6aacCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEqAARA6aaaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEqAARA6aad","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578567187+02:00","Elapsed":481598953740,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TD0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TD2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578588537+02:00","Elapsed":348321663755,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABgAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAGABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAGAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.57877832+02:00","Elapsed":453540068640,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TD0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TD2BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578835065+02:00","Elapsed":341336753755,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAFABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAFAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.578972087+02:00","Elapsed":477531290277,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAADQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAANABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAANAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579143132+02:00","Elapsed":483545271056,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABLABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABLAAStwkycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABLAAStwkyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABLAAStwkydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABLAAStwkyb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579162932+02:00","Elapsed":357579232455,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEMABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEMAARA6aecCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEMAARA6aebCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEMAARA6aedCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAEMAARA6aea","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579353261+02:00","Elapsed":421586052130,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAkABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAkAARKfYyaCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAkAARKfYycCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAkAARKfYydCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAkAARKfYyb","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579412518+02:00","Elapsed":483603738895,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAErABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAErAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579543175+02:00","Elapsed":469601115599,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L5kBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"L5mBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579671401+02:00","Elapsed":526642538872,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.579735499+02:00","Elapsed":484559610095,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.583224731+02:00","Elapsed":421532738508,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L5kBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"L5mBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABgAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAGABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAGAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:19:04.669507054+02:00","Elapsed":512726723317,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1l8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1l+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAADlABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADlAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADlAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADlAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAADlAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:20:14.995621526+02:00","Elapsed":300000973655,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"2MkBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"2MmBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:20:15.239335622+02:00","Elapsed":300181293276,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"59ABAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"59CBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:29.521836705+02:00","Elapsed":300155708728,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"59ABAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"59CBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWgATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWgAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:30.373201686+02:00","Elapsed":300000988633,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"59ABAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"59CBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAWAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAWAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:32.382382327+02:00","Elapsed":300000902894,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"59ABAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"59CBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAVAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAVAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:36.377313703+02:00","Elapsed":300000895533,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WqMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WqOBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAABAABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAEAABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:38.884408486+02:00","Elapsed":300000711393,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1vMBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"1vOBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAUQATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUQAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:39.158811929+02:00","Elapsed":300000949586,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WqMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WqOBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA/ABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAD8ABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:39.88054289+02:00","Elapsed":300000945903,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1vMBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"1vOBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAUAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAUAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:40.164135357+02:00","Elapsed":300001014901,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WqMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"WqOBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA9ABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAD0ABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:41.913311633+02:00","Elapsed":300000886524,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"D8iBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACNABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACNAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACNAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACNAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACNAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:42.668720528+02:00","Elapsed":300001015096,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m6cBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"m6eBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAACQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAJABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAJAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:43.139409928+02:00","Elapsed":300149229267,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"D8iBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACMABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACMAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACMAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACMAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACMAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:43.664475206+02:00","Elapsed":300001022079,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m6cBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"m6eBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAACQAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAJABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAJAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:43.989656746+02:00","Elapsed":300000952187,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"D8iBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACKABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACKAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACKAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACKAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACKAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:45.666936894+02:00","Elapsed":300001030328,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m6cBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"m6eBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAABwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAHABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAHAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:45.993143235+02:00","Elapsed":300001009770,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"D8gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"D8iBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAACGABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACGAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACGAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACGAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAACGAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:49.676310546+02:00","Elapsed":300003448073,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"m6cBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"m6eBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAAwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAADABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAADAAQX05iP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:49.995254732+02:00","Elapsed":300000778468,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ih0BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ih2BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAQAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAQAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:56.380981056+02:00","Elapsed":300000727512,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"51wBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"51yBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAFEAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:56.472472677+02:00","Elapsed":300177094631,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"51wBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"51yBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAFEAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAFEABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:57.314044368+02:00","Elapsed":300000964156,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ih0BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ih2BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAPwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPwAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:57.402180933+02:00","Elapsed":300000776706,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"51wBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"51yBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAE8AHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAE8ABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAE8ABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAE8ABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAE8ABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:59.305561799+02:00","Elapsed":300000851660,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ih0BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ih2BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAPQATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAPQAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:21:59.386604223+02:00","Elapsed":300000688760,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"51wBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"51yBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAEsAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEsABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEsABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEsABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAEsABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:03.307730702+02:00","Elapsed":300000948514,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ih0BAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ih2BgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOQATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOQAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:03.41167223+02:00","Elapsed":300000916666,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jqwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jqyBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAmABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAACYABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:05.030135451+02:00","Elapsed":300000910061,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wqwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wqyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAANwATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANwAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:05.315465433+02:00","Elapsed":300001003118,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jqwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jqyBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAlABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAACUABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:06.014186656+02:00","Elapsed":300000961613,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wqwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wqyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAANgATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:06.309105254+02:00","Elapsed":300000829673,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jqwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jqyBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAjABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAACMABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:08.018904462+02:00","Elapsed":300000946184,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wqwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wqyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAANAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:08.309434824+02:00","Elapsed":300000899587,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jqwBAAABAAAAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jqyBgAABAAIAAAAAAmlkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQJpZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAfABECaWQBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAJpZAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAB8ABK3CTF4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:12.035713459+02:00","Elapsed":300000960086,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wqwBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"wqyBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:12.311792317+02:00","Elapsed":300000962489,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X3MBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoNBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"X3OBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoNBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDQRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAABACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAAAEABEp9hYQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:14.345009407+02:00","Elapsed":300001132288,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nm0BAAABAAAAAAAABWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"nm2BgAABAAMAAAAABWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAAAQABBWdyYXBoCGZhY2Vib29rA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwASA2FwaQhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AA2FwaQhmYWNlYm9vawNjb20AAAUAAQAAADsAGARzdGFyBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAARzdGFyBGMxMHIIZmFjZWJvb2sDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AAS5PNgP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:14.381037264+02:00","Elapsed":300141518705,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lkgBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"lkiBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDURZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB1ACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAAHUABGyxD4Q=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:14.500323742+02:00","Elapsed":300156437414,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AiABAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AiCBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAvwAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:26.934442981+02:00","Elapsed":152389423,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"owgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"owiBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAsQAErcJMXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:27.437899833+02:00","Elapsed":42476547,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RxYBAAABAAAAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RxaBgAABAAcAAAAABGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABBGFwaXMGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAABQABAAAAIAATBHBsdXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FZQRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FZARwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FiwRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FZgRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FigRwbHVzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIAAESn2FcQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:28.481575912+02:00","Elapsed":5133388,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kUUBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"kUWBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAADEAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAADEABGyxD5sIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAADEABGyxD5wIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAADEABGyxD50IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAADEABGyxD5o=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:28.928068754+02:00","Elapsed":11231884,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LzEBAAABAAAAAAAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"LzGFgwABAAAAAQAACWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABCWdvb2dsZWFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBjGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIJZ29vZ2xlYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:29.351633567+02:00","Elapsed":179105,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"wwkBAAABAAAAAAAADmVuY3J5cHRlZC10Ym4wB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"wwmBgAABAAYAAAAADmVuY3J5cHRlZC10Ym4wB2dzdGF0aWMDY29tAAABAAEOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD2QOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD4oOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD2YOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD4sOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD3EOZW5jcnlwdGVkLXRibjAHZ3N0YXRpYwNjb20AAAEAAQAAAOEABGyxD2U=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:42.884445393+02:00","Elapsed":174091273,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+wABAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"+wCBgAABAAYAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEWABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEWAARKfYVfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEWAARA6bhfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEWAARA6adfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEWAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEWAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:47.683796572+02:00","Elapsed":44918330,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t0gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"t0iBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAnAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:47.732884776+02:00","Elapsed":49139728,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hV4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"hV6BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAABMABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABMAARssQ+aCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABMAARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABMAARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAABMAARssQ+c","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:48.066724209+02:00","Elapsed":5829756,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"EHIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"EHKFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:48.070015796+02:00","Elapsed":198783,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ivUBAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ivWFgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:48.07197542+02:00","Elapsed":228327,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zcUBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"zcWBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAADwAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAPABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAPAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:48.147478658+02:00","Elapsed":75784848,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RFoBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"RFqFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:48.958820798+02:00","Elapsed":213488,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tTgBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"tTiFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:22:50.221730875+02:00","Elapsed":237613,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IeIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"IeKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAABFAAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.217952398+02:00","Elapsed":5282320818,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/ewBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"/eyBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMiwdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTGYHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxxB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIoHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxk","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.226466214+02:00","Elapsed":3289354910,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X4QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"X4SBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAhAAEbLEPXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.234077839+02:00","Elapsed":3972936287,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"X4QBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"X4SBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGwAESn2FXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.236193093+02:00","Elapsed":2970221672,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IeIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"IeKBgAABAAEAAAAAA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABA3NzbAdnc3RhdGljA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGgAEQmYBXg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.236342115+02:00","Elapsed":4301371784,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j1sBAAABAAAAAAAABHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j1uBgAABAAQAAAAABHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQR1bml4DXN0YWNrZXhjaGFuZ2UDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZQFFBHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUEdW5peA1zdGFja2V4Y2hhbmdlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEl2WBRQR1bml4DXN0YWNrZXhjaGFuZ2UDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZcFF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.238947355+02:00","Elapsed":2696429663,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/ewBAAABAAAAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"/eyBgAABAAYAAAAAB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmnigdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2QHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6adxB2NvbnNlbnQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQOmnZQdjb25zZW50Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEDpp2YHY29uc2VudAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARA6aeL","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.249809877+02:00","Elapsed":4317123514,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"j1sBAAABAAAAAAAABHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"j1uBgAABAAQAAAAABHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQR1bml4DXN0YWNrZXhjaGFuZ2UDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZQFFBHVuaXgNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABJdlQUUEdW5peA1zdGFja2V4Y2hhbmdlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEl2WBRQR1bml4DXN0YWNrZXhjaGFuZ2UDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAASXZcFF","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.437807943+02:00","Elapsed":1890385760,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"zlgBAAABAAAAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"zliBgAABAAQAAAAABGFqYXgKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwNjb20AAAEAAQRhamF4Cmdvb2dsZWFwaXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAEIABkKZ29vZ2xlYXBpcwFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ACmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEIAARKfYVfCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEIAARssQ9fCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEIAAStwkxf","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.603540464+02:00","Elapsed":70911947,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vAwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"vAyBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAPAATAAEkC","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.782224145+02:00","Elapsed":81464090,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7pgBAAABAAAAAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"7piBgAABAA0AAAAAAWkFc3RhY2sFaW1ndXIDY29tAAABAAHADAAFAAEAAAErACYBaQVzdGFjawVpbWd1cgNjb20DY2RuCmNsb3VkZmxhcmUDbmV0AMAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQAyPALwABAAEAAAErAARoEBkiwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAbIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQHCLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEAEjwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAAI8AvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQGCLALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB8iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAaIsAvAAEAAQAAASsABGgQAiPALwABAAEAAAErAARoEB0iwC8AAQABAAABKwAEaBAeIg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.791272903+02:00","Elapsed":91002356,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gRsBAAABAAAAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"gRuBgAABAAIAAAAAA2xoNRFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNsaDURZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAADHACYMZ29vZ2xlaG9zdGVkAWwRZ29vZ2xldXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAxnb29nbGVob3N0ZWQBbBFnb29nbGV1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQAAAMcABEJmAYQ=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.824175637+02:00","Elapsed":74608095,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"yIYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"yIaFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dxBnb29nbGUtYW5hbHl0aWNzA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBgGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3EGdvb2dsZS1hbmFseXRpY3MDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||google-analytics.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.985084151+02:00","Elapsed":289574,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jl0BAAABAAAAAAAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"jl2FgwABAAAAAQAABnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAAAQABBnNlY3VyZQpxdWFudHNlcnZlA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIGc2VjdXJlCnF1YW50c2VydmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantserve.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:26.9852554+02:00","Elapsed":437348,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"iMQBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"iMSBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dxFnb29nbGV0YWdzZXJ2aWNlcwNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRZ29vZ2xldGFnc2VydmljZXMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAB0ABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB0AARssQ+cCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB0AARssQ+bCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB0AARssQ+dCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAB0AARssQ+a","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:27.067117461+02:00","Elapsed":94882930,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hEEBAAABAAAAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"hEGBgAABAAMAAAAAAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAAAQABAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQAABQABAAAAEAAmAnNiEXNjb3JlY2FyZHJlc2VhcmNoA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAACc2IRc2NvcmVjYXJkcmVzZWFyY2gDY29tB2VkZ2VrZXkDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAAQABkFZTE4NzkCZTcKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWUxODc5AmU3CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAQAAQXJiH9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:27.084592377+02:00","Elapsed":99828867,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ZNcBAAABAAAAAAAAAnFhB3NvY2tldHMNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ZNeBgAABAAEAAAAAAnFhB3NvY2tldHMNc3RhY2tleGNoYW5nZQNjb20AAAEAAQJxYQdzb2NrZXRzDXN0YWNrZXhjaGFuZ2UDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAATG/M4Z","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:27.396915672+02:00","Elapsed":96398259,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fgsBAAABAAAAAAAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQAB","Answer":"fguFgwABAAAAAQAADHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAAAQABDHNlY3VyZXB1YmFkcwFnC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAABgABAAAACgBmGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIMc2VjdXJlcHViYWRzAWcLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||g.doubleclick.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:27.97310368+02:00","Elapsed":245854,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"i5MBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"i5OBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUCcm8AAAEAAQlhZHNlcnZpY2UGZ29vZ2xlAnJvAAAFAAEAAAAnABwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQACHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAnAARKfYWbCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAnAARKfYWcCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAnAARKfYWdCHBhZ2VhZDQ2AWwLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAnAARKfYWa","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:28.048515979+02:00","Elapsed":75653147,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"LmsBAAABAAAAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"LmuBgAABAAUAAAAACWFkc2VydmljZQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEJYWRzZXJ2aWNlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAUAAQAAAAUAHAhwYWdlYWQ0NgFsC2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrA25ldAAIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABK3CTJwIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABK3CTJ0IcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABK3CTJoIcGFnZWFkNDYBbAtkb3VibGVjbGljawNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAAUABK3CTJs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:28.059873375+02:00","Elapsed":87007360,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IFkBAAABAAAAAAAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"IFmFgwABAAAAAQAAA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAAAQABA2NsYw1zdGFja292ZXJmbG93A2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBdGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDY2xjDXN0YWNrb3ZlcmZsb3cDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||clc.stackoverflow.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:40:29.264997697+02:00","Elapsed":189340,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"trEBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAE=","Answer":"trGBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAABIAGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAABwAAQAAABIAECYgAAAoMAIAAAAAAAAAAFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:41:21.711750771+02:00","Elapsed":278745610,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+YBAAABAAAAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"Y+aBgAABAAEAAAAACWlhbmF3aG9pcwN2aXAFaWNhbm4Db3JnAAABAAEJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAAUABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:41:21.782776223+02:00","Elapsed":63145803,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Y+YBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAE=","Answer":"Y+aBgAABAAIAAAAABXdob2lzBGlhbmEDb3JnAAABAAEFd2hvaXMEaWFuYQNvcmcAAAUAAQAAAB0AGQlpYW5hd2hvaXMDdmlwBWljYW5uA29yZwAJaWFuYXdob2lzA3ZpcAVpY2FubgNvcmcAAAEAAQAAAB0ABMAALzs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:41:21.846992765+02:00","Elapsed":419362221,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vOABAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAE=","Answer":"vOCBgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAAcAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAqQAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAEwAAAAAAAAAAAEYFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAABwAAQAAASsAECABBQAAMQAAAAAAAAAAAEY=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:41:22.165764937+02:00","Elapsed":91519986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7IgBAAABAAAAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"7IiBgAABAAMAAAAABXdob2lzBGFyaW4DbmV0AAABAAEFd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMfUAC4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMcFGi4Fd2hvaXMEYXJpbgNuZXQAAAEAAQAAASsABMdHAC4=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:41:22.373400851+02:00","Elapsed":300490205,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nQQBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"nQSBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:23.393904358+02:00","Elapsed":5232813631,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nQQBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"nQSBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:23.465479055+02:00","Elapsed":4300958926,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"nQQBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"nQSBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:23.479027151+02:00","Elapsed":2314240874,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"MHUBAAABAAAAAAAABTEzMzd4AnRvAAABAAE=","Answer":"MHWBgAABAAIAAAAABTEzMzd4AnRvAAABAAEFMTMzN3gCdG8AAAEAAQAAASsABGgfEQMFMTMzN3gCdG8AAAEAAQAAASsABGgfEAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:50.215513656+02:00","Elapsed":216403367,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3EwBAAABAAAAAAAADWRqdjk5c3hvcXB2MTEKY2xvdWRmcm9udANuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"3EyFgwABAAAAAQAADWRqdjk5c3hvcXB2MTEKY2xvdWRmcm9udANuZXQAAAEAAQ1kanY5OXN4b3FwdjExCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AAAGAAEAAAAKAGQZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3Rlcg1kanY5OXN4b3FwdjExCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||djv99sxoqpv11.cloudfront.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:53.948225709+02:00","Elapsed":286344,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kCQBAAABAAAAAAAAA2x4MQZkeW5jZG4CY2MAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"kCSBgAABAAIAAAAAA2x4MQZkeW5jZG4CY2MAAAEAAQNseDEGZHluY2RuAmNjAAABAAEAAAErAARoEiboA2x4MQZkeW5jZG4CY2MAAAEAAQAAASsABGgSJ+g=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:54.029236366+02:00","Elapsed":91990050,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"E04BAAABAAAAAAAACnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"E06FgwABAAAAAQAACnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABAAEKcnVubWV3aXZlbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAVhlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyCnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||runmewivel.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:44:54.112287713+02:00","Elapsed":187196,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IKABAAABAAAAAAAAA2pzYwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"IKCFgwABAAAAAQAAA2pzYwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQABA2pzYwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDanNjBG1naWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mgid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:45:08.961053714+02:00","Elapsed":190669,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"9I4BAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"9I6BgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAABWIABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.60057394+02:00","Elapsed":5222959570,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TfkBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TfmBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGhZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaVk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.610481636+02:00","Elapsed":5235398771,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ssBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4suBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAAGAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.625478527+02:00","Elapsed":2240343788,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ssBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4suBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.650972892+02:00","Elapsed":5272182458,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TfkBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TfmBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.651122136+02:00","Elapsed":4272097408,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"TfkBAAABAAAAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"TfmBgAABAAIAAAAABmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQZhZGF3YXkDb3JnAAABAAEAAAErAARoGGlZBmFkYXdheQNvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYaFk=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.651218141+02:00","Elapsed":2266701075,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"4ssBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"4suBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAcHAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:48:57.65135839+02:00","Elapsed":4269236800,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"DmsBAAABAAAAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"DmuBgAABAAEAAAAACmhvc3RzLWZpbGUDbmV0AAABAAEKaG9zdHMtZmlsZQNuZXQAAAEAAQAABToABGsWq48=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:49:37.632119833+02:00","Elapsed":13243678,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"THMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"THOBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dxFtYWx3YXJlZG9tYWlubGlzdANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cRbWFsd2FyZWRvbWFpbmxpc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAAbgAASP14I9","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:49:37.638489248+02:00","Elapsed":17413442,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rNoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"rNqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3BG1naWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mgid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:44.726768087+02:00","Elapsed":273460,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gagBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gaiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:44.744236487+02:00","Elapsed":240615,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JTgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"JTiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:44.749547088+02:00","Elapsed":169210,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vWUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"vWWFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantcast.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:44.769402217+02:00","Elapsed":226391,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gmwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"gmyBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAgQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgQAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgQAEQmYBXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAgQAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.034519625+02:00","Elapsed":2262946057,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"tHgBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"tHiBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEPZm9yY2VzYWZlc2VhcmNoBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.058296351+02:00","Elapsed":5315187502,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"mWIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"mWKFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.058502336+02:00","Elapsed":5315427705,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+pgBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+piBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAANgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA2AATAAFDyAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAEwABQ8QJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADYABMAAUPACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA2AATAAFDv","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.058607187+02:00","Elapsed":4286031445,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gmwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"gmyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABHQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHQAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.058737943+02:00","Elapsed":5292329850,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gmwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"gmyBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABKQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.091358341+02:00","Elapsed":4320761725,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+pgBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+piBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAIgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAiAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIgAEwABQ8gJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAACIABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAiAATAAFDw","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.091512958+02:00","Elapsed":2295184551,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7kIBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"7kKBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.09158572+02:00","Elapsed":2354761259,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7kIBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"7kKBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.091683936+02:00","Elapsed":4362140020,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"7kIBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"7kKBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0ECXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.091743924+02:00","Elapsed":5365330068,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+pgBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"+piBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAANgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA2AATAAFDyAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAANgAEwABQ8QJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADYABMAAUPACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA2AATAAFDv","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:51:50.091802479+02:00","Elapsed":5323315441,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GJcBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"GJeBgAABAAMAAAAAA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABA3d3dwdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAABQABAAACVwANB2Ryb25lYmwDb3JnAAdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEHxln8Qdkcm9uZWJsA29yZwAAAQABAAACVwAEBYeXQg==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:03.862704632+02:00","Elapsed":239853213,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"98cBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAE=","Answer":"98eBgAABAAIAAAAAA3d3dwJjcwN1bm0DZWR1AAABAAEDd3d3AmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAUAAQAADg8AEwZuZXd3ZWICY3MDdW5tA2VkdQAGbmV3d2ViAmNzA3VubQNlZHUAAAEAAQAADg8ABEBqFBs=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:03.991788193+02:00","Elapsed":364443866,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"cEQBAAABAAAAAAAABTEzMzd4AnRvAAABAAE=","Answer":"cESBgAABAAIAAAAABTEzMzd4AnRvAAABAAEFMTMzN3gCdG8AAAEAAQAAASsABGgfEQMFMTMzN3gCdG8AAAEAAQAAASsABGgfEAM=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:07.97847145+02:00","Elapsed":77102866,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"L+oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"L+qBgAABAAUAAAAAA3JhdxFnaXRodWJ1c2VyY29udGVudANjb20AAAEAAQNyYXcRZ2l0aHVidXNlcmNvbnRlbnQDY29tAAAFAAEAAAAdABcGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlAIUGZ2l0aHViA21hcAZmYXN0bHkDbmV0AAABAAEAAAAdAASXZUCFBmdpdGh1YgNtYXAGZmFzdGx5A25ldAAAAQABAAAAHQAEl2WAhQZnaXRodWIDbWFwBmZhc3RseQNuZXQAAAEAAQAAAB0ABJdlwIU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:08.072583816+02:00","Elapsed":140362674,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"taIBAAABAAAAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"taKBgAABAAIAAAAABWRlbW9zCXdpcmVkZG90cwNjb20AAAEAAQVkZW1vcwl3aXJlZGRvdHMDY29tAAAFAAEAAAA7AA8Jd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAJd2lyZWRkb3RzA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEIs4M1g==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:09.672310854+02:00","Elapsed":98055231,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"FsEBAAABAAAAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAE=","Answer":"FsGBgAABAAEAAAAABWxpcHNpAmNhAAABAAEFbGlwc2kCY2EAAAEAAQAADhAABKCZTSU=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:10.508408289+02:00","Elapsed":87583308,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"q84BAAABAAAAAAAAA2x4MQZkeW5jZG4CY2MAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"q86FgwABAAAAAQAAA2x4MQZkeW5jZG4CY2MAAAEAAQNseDEGZHluY2RuAmNjAAAGAAEAAAAKAFUZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgNseDEGZHluY2RuAmNjAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||dyncdn.cc^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:11.395088484+02:00","Elapsed":208561,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"h2gBAAABAAAAAAAADWRqdjk5c3hvcXB2MTEKY2xvdWRmcm9udANuZXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"h2iBgAABAAQAAAAADWRqdjk5c3hvcXB2MTEKY2xvdWRmcm9udANuZXQAAAEAAQ1kanY5OXN4b3FwdjExCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AAABAAEAAAA7AAQ2wF6WDWRqdjk5c3hvcXB2MTEKY2xvdWRmcm9udANuZXQAAAEAAQAAADsABDbAXsQNZGp2OTlzeG9xcHYxMQpjbG91ZGZyb250A25ldAAAAQABAAAAOwAENsBejA1kanY5OXN4b3FwdjExCmNsb3VkZnJvbnQDbmV0AAABAAEAAAA7AAQ2wF7C","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:11.488059197+02:00","Elapsed":76913361,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"xLcBAAABAAAAAAAACnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"xLeFgwABAAAAAQAACnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABAAEKcnVubWV3aXZlbANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAVhlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyCnJ1bm1ld2l2ZWwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||runmewivel.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:11.605218051+02:00","Elapsed":178942,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ggUBAAABAAAAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQAB","Answer":"ggWBgAABAAIAAAAACGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABCGNzZXJ2aWNlCHVuZGVybmV0A29yZwAAAQABAAABKwAEaBh7UQhjc2VydmljZQh1bmRlcm5ldANvcmcAAAEAAQAAASsABGgYelE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:14.882380527+02:00","Elapsed":79344100,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ulQBAAABAAAAAAAABmJvdWRqYQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"ulSFgwABAAAAAQAABmJvdWRqYQNjb20AAAEAAQZib3VkamEDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFIZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgZib3VkamEDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||boudja.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:15.145343038+02:00","Elapsed":206466,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"1FkBAAABAAAAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"1FmBgAABAAEAAAAACXdpcmVkZG90cw5tZXRhbG9naWNzc29mdANjb20AAAEAAQl3aXJlZGRvdHMObWV0YWxvZ2ljc3NvZnQDY29tAAABAAEAAASvAAREQXpn","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:18.795257493+02:00","Elapsed":94873021,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"sZ4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQ==","Answer":"sZ6BgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwN6bmMCaXQAAAEAAQN3d3cDem5jAml0AAABAAEAAA4QAATBvXAq","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:25.475685508+02:00","Elapsed":389851248,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3tgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"3tiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:41.266941591+02:00","Elapsed":299234,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Ln8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"Ln+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:41.267048873+02:00","Elapsed":370750,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AjMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"AjOBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:41.454697716+02:00","Elapsed":215646242,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AH0BAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"AH2BgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:41.455106849+02:00","Elapsed":205552271,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8ssBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8suBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwhqdWdnY2FzaANjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cIanVnZ2Nhc2gDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAATYEqhP","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:42.398609839+02:00","Elapsed":123258994,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fSMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"fSOFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:49.982887736+02:00","Elapsed":187728,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"rxoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"rxqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantcast.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:50.009360533+02:00","Elapsed":186866,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"kIIBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"kIKFgwABAAAAAQAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIIbWl4cGFuZWwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mixpanel.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:50.150564922+02:00","Elapsed":189487,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"pngBAAABAAAAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"pniBgAABAAIAAAAABXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABBXF1b3JhA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAENFZX9wVxdW9yYQNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABCOpS5k=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:52:50.34232946+02:00","Elapsed":175973496,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jqUBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"jqWFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:08.929479074+02:00","Elapsed":284366,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"IUEBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"IUGBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:09.114629863+02:00","Elapsed":212316247,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WKMBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"WKOBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:09.149522378+02:00","Elapsed":248815373,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"Bf4BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"Bf6FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantcast.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:09.914676669+02:00","Elapsed":158897,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"obgBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"obiBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEwABQ8gJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAAUPACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDv","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:10.113657488+02:00","Elapsed":80285780,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"c9kBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"c9mFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3BG1naWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mgid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:53:12.442619138+02:00","Elapsed":188069,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"CikBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"CimFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:49.628102695+02:00","Elapsed":252847,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RVEBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RVGFgwABAAAAAQAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIIbWl4cGFuZWwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mixpanel.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.631228862+02:00","Elapsed":194183,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"jXIBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"jXKFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.667492434+02:00","Elapsed":312500,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6c0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"6c2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.73547092+02:00","Elapsed":321626,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ku0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"ku2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3BG1naWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mgid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.735653465+02:00","Elapsed":428027,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hBYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"hBaFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantcast.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.735826189+02:00","Elapsed":622701,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hx0BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"hx2FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:57:50.8346751+02:00","Elapsed":188730,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gsYBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gsaBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADIAABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:30.808060518+02:00","Elapsed":40072811510,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"254BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"256FgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAADIAABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:30.808183176+02:00","Elapsed":40073018778,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PgoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PgqBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA1gAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA1gAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA1gAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA1gAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA1gAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA1gAESn1HXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:30.981042914+02:00","Elapsed":41353181747,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YCMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"YCOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAMQARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAxAATAAFDvAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAMQAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADEABMAAUPECbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAxAATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:30.989957032+02:00","Elapsed":39357190440,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8pYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8paBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.033957992+02:00","Elapsed":41406107834,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+j8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"+j+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.034129948+02:00","Elapsed":38407016845,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8pYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8paBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.034267947+02:00","Elapsed":38405923774,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PgoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PgqBgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAA2gAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA2gAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA2gAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA2gAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA2gAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA2gAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.034371706+02:00","Elapsed":40406441680,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YCMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"YCOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAJgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAmAATAAFDyAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJgAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAACYABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAmAATAAFDx","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.038857946+02:00","Elapsed":25401052642,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PgoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PgqBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABKQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKQAEbLEPXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039030769+02:00","Elapsed":34385270521,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PgoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PgqBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAABGAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGAAEQOmmXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGAAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABGAAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039084488+02:00","Elapsed":26403790986,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"KEMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"KEOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039157301+02:00","Elapsed":40372024125,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"PgoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"PgqBgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAJAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJAAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJAAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJAAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.03924362+02:00","Elapsed":38410899638,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YCMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"YCOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAIQARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAhAATAAFDvAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAIQAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAACEABMAAUPICbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAhAATAAFDx","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039383603+02:00","Elapsed":33408068860,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8pYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8paBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039393004+02:00","Elapsed":40411442688,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YCMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"YCOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDvAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAAUPECbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039466895+02:00","Elapsed":40372293547,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+j8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"+j+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOgAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADoABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA6AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOgAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039530822+02:00","Elapsed":40415321140,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+j8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"+j+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOgAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADoABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA6AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOgAENuZdjA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039604146+02:00","Elapsed":26404701160,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"YCMBAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"YCOBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAABwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAHAATAAFDvAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAABwAEwABQ8gJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAAAcABMAAUPECbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAHAATAAFDw","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.039663127+02:00","Elapsed":37405501534,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8pYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8paBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.045975915+02:00","Elapsed":34392207453,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+j8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"+j+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.048681854+02:00","Elapsed":41426870582,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+j8BAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"+j+BgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.052451362+02:00","Elapsed":34398698791,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"8pYBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"8paBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T22:58:31.229173722+02:00","Elapsed":26593856455,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"VyYBAAABAAAAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"VyaBgAABAAEAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAAEAAQlsb2NhbGhvc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAA4QAARKfeBI","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:00:37.523347637+02:00","Elapsed":5213476504,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"x+YBAAABAAAAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"x+aBgAABAAEAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAAEAAQlsb2NhbGhvc3QDY29tAAABAAEAAA4PAARKfeBI","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:00:38.853149173+02:00","Elapsed":10795247,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6j8BAAABAAAAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AABwAAQ==","Answer":"6j+BgAABAAAAAQAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AABwAAQlsb2NhbGhvc3QDY29tAAAGAAEAAASjADoEZG5zMAh6b25lZWRpdANjb20ABHpvbmUIem9uZWVkaXQDY29tAFQt06sAAAlgAAABaAASdQAAABwg","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:00:38.915626698+02:00","Elapsed":56543961,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ztcBAAABAAAAAAAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"zteBgAABAAAAAQAACWxvY2FsaG9zdANjb20AAA8AAQlsb2NhbGhvc3QDY29tAAAGAAEAAARvADoEZG5zMAh6b25lZWRpdANjb20ABHpvbmUIem9uZWVkaXQDY29tAFQt06sAAAlgAAABaAASdQAAABwg","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:00:38.9746148+02:00","Elapsed":52766408,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"668BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"66+FgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXZvaWNlZml2ZQNjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwl2b2ljZWZpdmUDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||voicefive.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:10.495767681+02:00","Elapsed":239953,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RlkBAAABAAAAAAAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"RlmFgwABAAAAAQAACG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAAAQABCG1peHBhbmVsA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIIbWl4cGFuZWwDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mixpanel.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.497033287+02:00","Elapsed":287428,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"l7gBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"l7iFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwtkb3VibGVjbGljawNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAAGAAEAAAAKAFsZZmFrZS1mb3ItbmVnYXRpdmUtY2FjaGluZwh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAKaG9zdG1hc3RlcgN3d3cLZG91YmxlY2xpY2sDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doubleclick.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.497207419+02:00","Elapsed":323893,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"GmwBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"GmyFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXF1YW50Y2FzdANjb20AAAYAAQAAAAoAWRlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwlxdWFudGNhc3QDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||quantcast.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.597896001+02:00","Elapsed":189979,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"JhMBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"JhOFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwRtZ2lkA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBUGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3BG1naWQDY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||mgid.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.697547691+02:00","Elapsed":241542,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"3CgBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"3CiFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpkb3VibGVwaW1wA2NvbQAABgABAAAACgBaGWZha2UtZm9yLW5lZ2F0aXZlLWNhY2hpbmcId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8ACmhvc3RtYXN0ZXIDd3d3CmRvdWJsZXBpbXADY29tAAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||doublepimp.com^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.808987883+02:00","Elapsed":191642,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"oHoBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAE=","Answer":"oHqFgwABAAAAAQAAA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABAAEDd3d3DHRyYWZmaWNqdW5reQNuZXQAAAYAAQAAAAoAXBlmYWtlLWZvci1uZWdhdGl2ZS1jYWNoaW5nCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAApob3N0bWFzdGVyA3d3dwx0cmFmZmljanVua3kDbmV0AAABiJQAAAcIAAADhAAJOoAAAVGA","Result":{"IsFiltered":true,"Reason":3,"Rule":"||trafficjunky.net^","FilterID":1541267071},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:11.909940835+02:00","Elapsed":201188,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"v2YBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"v2aBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.268629184+02:00","Elapsed":46666420864,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t2oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t2qFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.268778193+02:00","Elapsed":46666622504,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"uKsBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"uKuBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.269227665+02:00","Elapsed":45673159157,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t2oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t2qFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.269344058+02:00","Elapsed":45673389002,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"+uMBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"+uOBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.301070218+02:00","Elapsed":43701293924,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t2oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t2qFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.301233139+02:00","Elapsed":43701530765,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"6/cBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"6/eBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.301375808+02:00","Elapsed":39697431053,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t2oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t2qFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.301495624+02:00","Elapsed":39697621948,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"RyoBAAABAAAAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"RyqBgAABAAEAAAAAD2ZvcmNlc2FmZXNlYXJjaAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.301865077+02:00","Elapsed":31694286412,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"t2oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"t2qFgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3Bmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAACZQABNjvJng=","Result":{"Reason":7},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.302010587+02:00","Elapsed":31694503051,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vxABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"vxCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAKwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAArAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAKwAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAACsABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAArAATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.486778335+02:00","Elapsed":45980779985,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AK8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AK+BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAfwAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAfwAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAfwAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAfwAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.486840204+02:00","Elapsed":47000270867,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AK8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AK+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAHgAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHgAESn1HXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHgAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHgAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAHgAEQmYBXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.486876073+02:00","Elapsed":47991329897,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vxABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"vxCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAOwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAOwAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAADsABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAA7AATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.49119638+02:00","Elapsed":46994422617,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.49379993+02:00","Elapsed":46996777205,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/0oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/0qBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.493832154+02:00","Elapsed":47007256594,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.493886783+02:00","Elapsed":46000134468,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J9wBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"J9yBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXSgJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.504662699+02:00","Elapsed":47018128697,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J9wBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"J9yBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdHAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXYwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0oCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.504760419+02:00","Elapsed":45015949293,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J9wBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"J9yBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.504785813+02:00","Elapsed":48012561313,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/0oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/0qBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.504858433+02:00","Elapsed":48009314035,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vxABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"vxCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAALgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAuAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAALgAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAAC4ABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAuAATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.514286602+02:00","Elapsed":40012673283,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vxABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"vxCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAAJwARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAnAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAJwAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAACcABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAnAATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.521716144+02:00","Elapsed":44016795861,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AK8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AK+BgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAiQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAiQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAiQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAiQAESn2FXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.521802436+02:00","Elapsed":33016550843,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AK8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AK+BgAABAAUAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAGAAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGAAEQOmnXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGAAESn2MXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGAAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAGAAErcJMXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.53651861+02:00","Elapsed":45044651170,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AK8BAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"AK+BgAABAAYAAAAAA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAAAQABA3d3dwpnb29nbGVhcGlzA2NvbQAABQABAAAAoQAZCmdvb2dsZWFwaXMBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAApnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAoQAEbLEPXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAoQAErcJMXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAoQAESn2FXwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAoQAEQOm4Xwpnb29nbGVhcGlzAWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAAoQAEQOmnXw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.536821087+02:00","Elapsed":41039941133,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoIHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4I=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.536832868+02:00","Elapsed":40035215945,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.53691124+02:00","Elapsed":44031995789,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"fHsBAAABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Answer":"fHuBgwABAAAAAAAAAmxiB19kbnMtc2QEX3VkcAEwATIDMTAwAjEwB2luLWFkZHIEYXJwYQAADAAB","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.536948552+02:00","Elapsed":137121815497,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"vxABAAABAAAAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQAB","Answer":"vxCBgAABAAUAAAAAAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAmVuCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAABQABAAAADgARAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQACbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAOAATAAFDxAmxiCGdyYXZhdGFyA2NvbQAAAQABAAAADgAEwABQ8AJsYghncmF2YXRhcgNjb20AAAEAAQAAAA4ABMAAUO8CbGIIZ3JhdmF0YXIDY29tAAABAAEAAAAOAATAAFDy","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.536978671+02:00","Elapsed":32030676186,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/0oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/0qBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.537108567+02:00","Elapsed":41040219193,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J9wBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"J9yBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdjAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXQQJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l0cCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.537161823+02:00","Elapsed":33034331991,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"gjMBAAABAAAAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"gjOBgAABAAIAAAAAB2FkZ3VhcmQDY29tAAABAAEHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUH4IHYWRndWFyZANjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABGgUHoI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.537226718+02:00","Elapsed":32033103782,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/0oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/0qBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.543089121+02:00","Elapsed":45051215236,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"J9wBAAABAAAAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQAB","Answer":"J9yBgAABAAQAAAAACXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdKAl3aG90cmFja3MCbWUAAAEAAQAAADsABDbmXRwJd2hvdHJhY2tzAm1lAAABAAEAAAA7AAQ25l2MCXdob3RyYWNrcwJtZQAAAQABAAAAOwAENuZdBA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.562766771+02:00","Elapsed":41065888867,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"/0oBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"/0qBgAABAAQAAAAAA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20AAAEAAQN3d3cFYXBwbGUDY29tAAAFAAEAAAATABsDd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAAABQABAAAAEwAyA3d3dwVhcHBsZQNjb20HZWRnZWtleQNuZXQLZ2xvYmFscmVkaXIGYWthZG5zA25ldAADd3d3BWFwcGxlA2NvbQdlZGdla2V5A25ldAtnbG9iYWxyZWRpcgZha2FkbnMDbmV0AAAFAAEAAAATABwFZTY4NTgFZHNjZTkKYWthbWFpZWRnZQNuZXQABWU2ODU4BWRzY2U5CmFrYW1haWVkZ2UDbmV0AAABAAEAAAATAAQX2Mro","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.579879528+02:00","Elapsed":33074541437,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.858568952+02:00","Elapsed":47361560427,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.866988+02:00","Elapsed":32360666511,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:58.982710896+02:00","Elapsed":46480878851,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:59.001539575+02:00","Elapsed":40499921478,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"SgkBAAABAAAAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAE=","Answer":"SgmBgAABAAEAAAAAA3d3dwlzbmlnZWx3ZWIDY29tAAABAAEDd3d3CXNuaWdlbHdlYgNjb20AAAEAAQAADhAABMC5FYg=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:10:59.001740539+02:00","Elapsed":44496760538,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"HCYBAAABAAAAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQAB","Answer":"HCaBgAABAAQAAAAAA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4AgNhcGkId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMDYXBpCHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEAAA4QAAS53LgEA2FwaQh3aGl0ZWhhdAJybwAAAQABAAAOEAAEudy4AQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:16:01.994358567+02:00","Elapsed":247843561,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WP0BAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"WP2BgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:43.997279384+02:00","Elapsed":145692432930,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ToMBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"ToOBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABp8ABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABp8ABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABp8ABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABp8ABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:44.002822969+02:00","Elapsed":179997380592,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lkwBAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"lkyBgAABAAYAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARCZgFkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEJmAYsGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQmYBZgZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAARCZgFxBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABEJmAWUGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAEQmYBig==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:44.002952765+02:00","Elapsed":139925937130,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"WP0BAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"WP2BgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAABZwABLncuAI=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:44.010225085+02:00","Elapsed":150701394944,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"lkwBAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"lkyBgAABAAYAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAD0AARssQ+KBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAPQABGyxD2YGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA9AAEbLEPZAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAD0AARssQ9lBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAPQABGyxD3EGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAAA9AAEbLEPiw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:44.010378961+02:00","Elapsed":134941580685,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"ToMBAAABAAAAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAE=","Answer":"ToOBgAABAAQAAAAACHdoaXRlaGF0AnJvAAABAAEId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAIId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAMId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAQId2hpdGVoYXQCcm8AAAEAAQAADhAABLncuAE=","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:20:44.052392356+02:00","Elapsed":185035446770,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"T6ABAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"T6CBgAABAAYAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkyKBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTIsGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMcQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAErAAStwkxkBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAASsABK3CTGYGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABKwAErcJMZQ==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:46:10.571304554+02:00","Elapsed":424362702,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"T6ABAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQ==","Answer":"T6CBgAABAAYAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEeAAStwkxxBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAR4ABK3CTIoGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHgAErcJMZgZnb29nbGUDY29tAAABAAEAAAEeAAStwkxlBmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAAEAAQAAAR4ABK3CTGQGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAAAQABAAABHgAErcJMiw==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:46:10.571429496+02:00","Elapsed":5433874926,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"hkABAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AABwAAQ==","Answer":"hkCBgAABAAEAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AABwAAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAcAAEAAACqABAqABRQQAwMBwAAAAAAAACL","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:46:10.646628321+02:00","Elapsed":60667460,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
{"Question":"AAgBAAABAAAAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAA8AAQ==","Answer":"AAiBgAABAAUAAAAABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAA8AAQZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAPAAEAAAJXABYACgVhc3BteAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAA8AAQAAAlcAGwAeBGFsdDIFYXNwbXgBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAZnb29nbGUDY29tAAAPAAEAAAJXABsAFARhbHQxBWFzcG14AWwGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAGZ29vZ2xlA2NvbQAADwABAAACVwAbADIEYWx0NAVhc3BteAFsBmdvb2dsZQNjb20ABmdvb2dsZQNjb20AAA8AAQAAAlcAGwAoBGFsdDMFYXNwbXgBbAZnb29nbGUDY29tAA==","Result":{},"Time":"2018-11-03T23:46:10.709210537+02:00","Elapsed":56342204,"IP":"10.100.2.111"}
